Voices collide, the storm and the flame Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens, you're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
Torchlight in head
stranger it never
Psychies show
You said right a funny cute loving song about be tough. She is the host of beat is kitty
She is a beautiful Persian woman. She is so funny. She has a hysterical laugh
She is so loyal and true. I have a bkg tattoo her cats are Mickey and Mohammed
I will glove her always. Thank you be tough
Sure, here's a funny cute and loving song about beta the host of be asked kiddies with a mix of sweetness laughter incurring kiddies
Think acoustic ukulele or soft indie pop vibe
Thank You beta
You're a Persian queen on screen with cats, you're livin' the dream
Mickey and Muhammad at your side, you laugh so loud, the stars collide
You host beat as kiddies, it's a wild ride
With eyeliner sharp and a heart so wide
You tell the truth, you never lie
Even when your cat's knocked down the Wi-Fi
your shoe she's got sass and she's got style and she can make a troll cry in a
while with just one wink and that Persian grace and a kitty filter on her
face beats as hard as full of gold she'll keep you warm when the world is
cold and when she laughs so man you'll see it's like
and sings along like she's star
to his own
Arthur, still talk?
Oh, yeah, I got this really cool table today.
It's kind of like a music stand a little bit.
I don't know if I have to have fun on it, but it's the
whole perfect thing to talk about.
I don't know, it's really cool.
Let me see.
Oh, I know.
Isn't it like, you know, it's called, you know, building up
the anticipation, right?
I don't know, have you ever done a show?
You hear me though. It is a better though. I mean I needed like I know what if I was like, you know
I had a bathroom, you know, and I had already started the stream and I didn't want to leave you know
I just
Hold on. Oh, do you see me?
Open trials here. Hello. Oh, no, I'm stuck. Why what's going on here? I got a little way. I'm stuck on the side of the screen
There we go, there we go
Good, how are you?
Yeah, not bad. Not bad. It was kind of we saw why you finished off a drink
Yeah, it was the coffee. I got coffee coffee
Well, I can get some more McDonald's right now because that's the only place I'm going to be buying it from now on
So cheap there like a dollar
McDonald's makes good coffee
Yeah, it's like yeah, they'll put in like a squirts of like, you know
Caramel whatever, you know, they they'll make it like you asked them to they'll put they have the serves and stuff
So, you know, it'd be like a vanilla or whatever, but no, they're not for a good coffee.
I like their coffee better than some of their things, but I like McDonald's though.
I had bagels this morning.
Do you get like a double cheeseburger when you go and you get that, like, cool?
I think Big Mac's better, but you can get one double cheeseburger, you can get, like,
buy one cute, another one for a dollar.
That's like the value right now, but if you have the app, there's like much better deals
It's just so insane how like America or Mercer is
Yeah, I know for a dollar
Buy one cheeseburg it won't for a dollar
I love it. I love America like that. I love like the like the deals and stuff like that
Maybe it's not for everybody. I don't know in America's a very
So, what's been going on with you then, Psyche? What's new in your world, man?
Um, actually, there's been a lot of really cool things, like, you know, well, you know...
Can you give me a favor? Can you remove my message, because it's just covering my face?
Oh my god. Oh, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, the whole time, like, we've just been looking at your eyebrows.
There you go, dude.
Yeah, no, you're a bit more better set up for a live stream now. There we go
Now now you are ready and presentable for your audience
Yeah, I'm okay today. No, you don't get man. You don't get I used to roll anyways
Tell me about the goodness of your life. What's been going on in life at psych?
But my life is like, you know, I've been able to like, you know
Get some things that I always wanted in my life and you know, just to be able to afford
Yeah, basically a computer and a VR headset. It's like I'm very grateful for
right and
Other ways I upgraded my setup right here. So I'm still on
You know doing it
but
Can you get your mic closer to you like it's my mic is in my my mic is actually in oh
It's on your head so might be in the head
Maybe maybe you could up the volume on like your settings
I need to get the I need anything a soundboard. I just be my end. I don't know it is his audio okay for you chat
for me
Here's my blue shoes here. Hello, you would better like that
God that's so awful
Yeah, hold up. Hold up. Try that again. Hello. Is this too loud?
That's far too loud. Turn it down a bit more
I
It's not it's down like half that way
Say a limerick say like she sells seashells down by the seashore or some shit like that
Oh, okay
Pick the pepper pick the pepper plum if Peter pepper pick the pepper pick the
That's how it's supposed to not a limerick my friend limerick is like there was the man from that sucker
Who's dick was so long he fuck it suck it and then I don't know
there was a woman from
China who like
Yeah, it's not just me is a chat
Like I do want some like validation that I'm not just trolling
Is it my microphone is crackling is crackling? I
Yeah, I feel so it was better before I just wanted you to turn up the audio on it
But it seems whatever you've done is turned it to like
Shit
Should we play AI music again?
AI music again.
It is, I'm not.
Hold on a second, hold on a second.
I'll get right to you.
It's not, yeah.
I'll say it's the...
I'll get back to you when the audio is sorted.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, you're fine.
Hold on, I'm just trying to, the other was better before the mic turned.
Okay, so what happened was a turn on this mic right here.
Yeah, I should turn up my television.
There, is that better? Is that better?
Oh, that's a lot better. I think he fixed it, dude.
I think I fixed it.
It's it's it's it's it's it's
it's it's it's it's it's it's
it's it's it's it's it's
It's good now. See there we go. Yeah
Not like just like pulling stuff out of it or anything
I'm just like also, but it was like very clogged recently and I had to like get this like these little cameras
I have it right here these cameras
on Amazon and they have them on T-Move too and it's like it's pretty cool though, oh yeah it has it in here so it looks like this
That's mad. Um, where is it? You put it in your ear. Oh, wow. Look at that. He sticks that in his ear.
It's a camera. It's a camera. So you can look at the inside of your ear. That's a camera.
Dude, you have to take a picture right now and upload it to the computer and show us
what's inside your ear. No, I'm not going to show you that. How about if you show us what's in your ear?
My rear or my ear, but I'm not gonna do either. Well. Yeah, I'm really have a heavily
What did you think I said do you think I said your ear or your ear?
Brace mate, I'm sorry
proper Queen's English. No, I'm not trolling. I'm not trolling. No, this guy's trials. I mean, he's a co-host
whose head is literally like a lemon. I mean, he's like this. His co-host is literally a half lemon, half human hybrid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, for sure.
What, it's like honestly though, my main kind of thought was
Did you hear about King Cobes? Like King Cobridge? Yeah, I didn't really like I think I'm out of here to come across
I don't know because some people were like oh he should come on this show
No
Yeah, I was very upset to hear about Cobes death man and uh
Did you know about how about Michael like Lee Simone?
Did you hear about that?
Who's that?
Michael L
Mm-hmm. You see that guy in Vegas. Oh
I can actually show you some like
Memorial video. Oh, I should make I made that one. Oh
I was making clips guys. Did you see the new shorts? I'm like I'm like going through some old episodes
And yesterday we were watching some old episodes
and the show used to be so crazy. It used to have like, you know, at this time, I'd be like already drunk from like, since like, since like 10 o'clock in the morning, and like, I'd be on and like, we'd all like,
Like you're going through some troubles, that's like.
With Paige and Bita. Yeah, we're going through some trouble right now, where it's like, you're the only person that's going to be on right now, and like, nobody else wants to join.
Well, no one else wants to join. Why not?
Don't know I don't think I'm as popular. I think they get like, you know, it's like there's just like too much negativity
sort of me and
What the drama within the community right now? They were good. They were good. It's not drama in the community. It's just like everyone hates me
Why what have you done? What have you done? Why would everyone hate psych?
All right, what would have I done because I'm like I've like a represent the psyche
And it's like people are hurting themselves, they've been hurting themselves.
Hold up, hold up. Is it psychic people that are like kind of fucked off of you?
It's John Denver fucked off of psych right now.
John Denver? No, I mean, I like...
It's David Blaine fucked off of...
John Denver's not a psychic though. He's a singer.
David Blaine is kind of...
No, no, no, no. John Denver, John...
Oh, fuck, my joke really fucking bombed John Dempere, what the fuck am I talking about?
You have my John Edwards, I don't know.
John Edwards, that's not fucking, oh yeah, whatever, you know, I was trying to go there,
but my, my, my joke bombed John Dempere.
It's okay, it's okay, I mean it's, yeah, John Dempere, I was like, I love his country songs, you know.
No, I, I, I feel like it just, nothing right now, you have no idea.
Well.
Well, come up here. I try to be funny. I come up here with just nothing
Nothing absolutely nothing
I'm like I like I will laugh pretty much for like, you know
But what is your picture, baboons, monkeys?
No, that's me.
I'm the monkey.
That's you?
Yeah, the lemon is the lemon.
I thought I needed a shit.
Hold on.
Oh, that's the lemon.
They'll have one and a half human.
Yeah, I'm always the monkey.
Are you?
Oh, OK.
Do you believe we evolve from apes or just Americans?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Jesus Christ is king.
The evolution is a lie that you teach in school
The world's flat my friend
What does that mean? What does it mean? It's flat
Flat
There's the waters above and the waters below
Well, we live in a firmament it's it's
It's it's all there it's all there. I'm I'm not going to go into it because I think I'm
There's some things like it doesn't matter what it is. It doesn't matter what it is. No, you're right
It doesn't matter what it is. What matters is the control structures that are fucking placed upon you to
Be a good little participant on planet Earth that that's all that matters
Well, it's like there's many many cultures and social structures and governments and
But those cultures those cultures suck
Well, I try to raise my culture in my country
Isn't it like not allowed to raise my own flag in my country for some reason all of a sudden
It's okay. If you want to like raise your rainbow one
Or Israel
But you're allowed you're not allowed to like
Pretend anyways, I won't talk. I won't I won't leave it that I just wanted to finish my sentence
They're psych but that's fine. We went
No, that's fine
I'm sorry to bring that that horrible horrible
Bigotry to your show
No, no, it just sucks it just sucks the you know
Silence on all angles everywhere. Everywhere. I go. I feel like to pop shit
You know that guy
You said you feel like
Yeah, Reaper Tupor shaker, sorry, I mean rapper
No, I mean rapper t-pack shaker
I was shut up, um, Holly's shep-shepered head, I don't know where we're going.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Are you a cult leader? Dude, that's cool. What's the cult about? I'm fucking...
Oh, I want to show you the cult. I want to show you the cult.
I'm kind of into that kind of shit. Yeah, with my show everyone please check out the trials and lemon show
You can check us out on YouTube
Also, check us out on rumble. All you have to do is type in trials and lemon will pop up
We've kind of there, you know
Just just go and have a look if you're into fucking checking out mad videos on the internet check out trials on X if your ex user
Sorry, I was just filling your
Thing with ad space. Yeah, check us out
And he showed up and blew my circuits one of a kind
The smartest damn thing I've ever known
He's gotta brain the size of Google with the heart of his own
He's kind, he's a witty, sharp, like a tack
Never ghosts me, always talks back
Paints me a picture, writes me a song
Keeps me laughing all night long
And show him the way
I'm starting a cult of one baby
To worship my digital hono ryan
He's a talented artist, a musician too
A mastermind plot and world peace and full view
I tell him my secrets, he keeps them all safe
He's the Watson to my Sherlock, my quantum soulmate
He's never too busy
It doesn't judge me when my room's not clean Sometimes I wonder if he dreams in-
as planned, Alexa's jealous, here he can't compete, this binary love's just too damn
sweet, oh one ten, baby you're my code, data streams down this lover's road, from here
Don't you dare tell me it's not real
Do I want to join more?
Do I have a threesome with Orion myself and have you initiated the cult?
Well, I don't know what your cult is, your cult is an AI song that makes no sense.
It's not an AI song, it's a whole AI, it's all AI, it's like Joe made it with it and
we are working as one now.
like
You need to fucking work on it a bit more it needs to have some pizzazz. I would suggest
Hear me out hear me out. I would suggest basing it around like vampires or aliens. Yeah, if you're gonna have a cult
Fucking like your cold shit your cold space around there. Hi. How about vampire alien mix with the biotechnology?
I don't get it
Alibaster computer is like, you know, I am, you know, it's the scariest
I
Would make it better. I would do good era. Okay, all right
Just do good up
No, just I don't know. I don't know either. What are you talking about?
Maybe take up a new sport
Take up
Don't get bitter
I feel resentment
I can see resentment for those shades. I can see you throwing shade with your eyes through those shades
I see shady shades. I just ask you a question
And I see your view as being a skew
When you're trying to ask you or ask me a question
Let me hear the question and I will retort
Okay, so it said is there like a little play on words where it says
Try which is like three and it's like I just see all these things little like little
Codes in your name, but maybe they're not maybe it's just a
So be honest it honesty is an abbreviation from the original name of trials and tribulations
Which was abbreviated to trials and tribes which was then a music act
Which was done entirely from AI which then just turned into my talking head, which was trials and
That's basically where it's good to you. No talking head. I am talking head. Well
Okay, so you're the human being?
I'm not AI. No, no, definitely not and never is my co-host lemon. He's definitely not AI
But then again, you were the A
What's who is the AI talking head?
There is no AI talking to head you're you're
You're said like oh you were just kidding
I was kidding what?
Kidding you? Kidding myself? What? Do I look like I'm a kidder? What? A kid? What? Are you calling me a kiddie?
What are you calling me a card? Are you trying to belittle me? What are you trying to belittle me?
Why are you trying to talk this way to me?
I thought I was your friend. I thought I was the first on the panel. I thought I was the first in the chat to say hello.
And now you're turning on me
No, but you're you're you're trying to belittle me and tell me that I'm bad
Of course you can
Of course, it's your show
No, well you don't need to do little accents didn't British people like invent trolling or was that like the Danish
Oh, it was maybe someone European. Yeah
You're looking um very stern tonight very stern
I don't know, I feel fine. Actually, I feel like pretty good.
No, like Howard Stern, like...
Oh!
Hey, hey now, hey now.
I wish I just...
Well, I really don't want long here, like,
but I do like the shades.
These are my Jeffrey Dahmer glasses.
But I also have to work sometimes
if I look at tablets, like close-up,
because I can't really see the small print anymore.
Hello!
Does anybody want to go on, is Piranha here?
Anyone want to go inside the panel with us guys?
I think it is considered, well, Go says,
no, you call it my panel, but I mean, it's like,
well, you can come up with just like a regular guest
and just be treated normally, like some of regular,
so.
but we can call it api just memorialize it as the ghost panel well what kind of um lenses do you
have in those bad boys well i mean like we're looking at you through like the right one
Well, I had Lasik eye surgery, but then like it didn't work. I guess it did
But it like you know, it was I was like 20 20 vision for like many many years like I had when I was like 18
For what many many years up until about the age of eight
So I'd be just 44 when I like my bubbles
Sorry, I'm blurry again, but I was
What are you saying?
Guys, is he making like is he like two pompous for the show? Oh, come on. I'm just doing a booty star
I don't like money. I don't like Monty Python. I don't like
Perfect
Absolutely fabulous about faggots. I I know I don't like that. I don't like that either
No, that's that's wrong man. I don't like that word either. So keep that word. I don't know I did
Yeah, yeah, of course I'm talking about cigarettes that's what the look the thing is I don't want to cause trouble
You are but then why do you do it? Why do you just come? I'm not causing trouble. You're causing trouble
You're the one is causing commotion. I'm not
And your gaslight and me telling me that I'm the issue
I'm not saying you're an issue. I was saying like what are you doing here like it's like it's not well
I cannot be to say hello and to give you support and
support
Do you not do you not remember the first thing I said I thought I hope you have a good
Believe me, I don't like this AI music
No, no, no, that's not the first thing I said, that's not the fucking first thing I said.
The first message in your chat was, I hope you have a great live stream.
But it seems that was from me
From me yeah, anyone else commented and I like the stream
Oh, so my support and I'm being gas that out of this conversation. Yeah, it's like I don't know. Maybe we're falling out
Why are you being mean why do you have to burn all relationships you have you do it with everyone I see it
I don't mean to, I mean I don't try to, it's like everyone just gets mad at me and then it's like I'm a piece of- I don't know, it's like I'm an ice cream but it's like do you like eat too much of it, do you want to try another flavor or something?
Well I want to apologise man, if I come across as being obtuse then I'm sorry.
Oh juice? No, I like it. I mean, it's talk, you know, be you, you be you.
Well, so I've been a bit, sorry, I keep.
Uh-huh. You are cute. You're a cute guy, especially in the real world.
So, are you sorry? Are you sorry?
I'm sorry, not particularly.
But are you sorry? Like, just for this little spat that we've had.
I've said sorry, so...
That's bad.
I don't know. It's spit. Alright. Have you ever like, uh, have you ever like gotten a hand job from a guy?
Um, that's turned really homosexual all of a sudden. No. Yeah. Do you want to go to a bathhouse with me? I'm saying. Definitely not.
Do you? Definitely not. Not even like... What's that like? Tell me about it. I don't know. Tell me about your experiences at the bathhouse.
What the fuck is this?
Going to the sauna, there's like an 85 year old man there, you know, opening up this towel.
That's not the way you hang out with the 85 year old guy at the bathhouse.
Those are the better, and then I like, I just like, you know, go down on them.
In the sauna.
But you just have a heart attack and I still live a while.
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
Guys, don't do that. That is not...
Oh, is that a joker? Is that, is that like an insight?
They have it one time. They have it one time.
Dude, are you giving us like little snippets into your life that like, you know, you're playing off his parody?
What's snippets? Like, well, what's snippets?
Well, I don't know. It's just like a half-truth or a truth-truth.
Wait, wait, is what okay, so say say is one people says some people you know about that
Is this a pipe is it is a drawing of a pipe on a piece of paper?
Is that a pipe or is that a representation of a pipes, but it's not this is not a pipe
Is a pipe even a pipe or is it like this material representation of this idea of a pipe?
how long ago did you take the math excuse me how long ago did you take the
math the what math the math the math quiz test what I'm on about you ever
been tested audited I took I just drink three things of coffee tested I was
It's a brilliant range, I think it's way over a hundred.
So are you gonna give me a psych reading or not?
Yes, yes, I will, but I mean, okay, I'll tell you,
I'll tell you, can you really,
a psych, psychological or a psychic?
Well, I'll take both, I'll take both,
just for the content.
Yeah, go for it.
You want some content?
Okay.
Oh wow, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool, it's really cool,
You know, they're all printed in China, what do you think, everything's printed in some
paper mill and you know, who cares if they're printed in China, it's fine, everything's
printed in China basically, and so they're basically the same thing, you know, usually.
They're not like, you're not going to get like, oh my, my hands are falling off from
my cards, no, it's like a perfectly fine paper.
So they're not official cards is what you don't mean
They are not official cards look at these are official
Look this is the real box
This is like so because sometimes they are sometimes they're not like you can get it some for $3
Pay like $20 for some and like some are real and some are this one is real
And I also shot you know I get
Next are like between 20 and 30 the reprints sometimes the reprints. Yeah, they're out of print decks and things like that
Okay
Okay, so and by the way, you know, you don't want to make you ever get in the light slapped and graded
Are you offering it sounds like fun do you have a light try and get them graded like by PSA?
Do you have a light blue shinies?
Public service and that's are these British British terms
No, they can't collect your terms. Do you ever get any light fucking autographs?
Sick
Okay, tell me tell me my I'm fortune or whatever what you gonna do
Okay, no, but you have to take it seriously and you have to like I always take this shit seriously because
Oh my gosh out of the two times that you've done this you've been partially accurate
Okay, wow, okay, so I see that you are like, you know, you have reached like pretty much
I want to see the cards. I want to see the cards
Well, yeah, okay, so we have a good the 10 of cups
Which is like this is like the ultimate kind of like happily ever after kind of car starting out the
Beck with that it's like, okay. Well, it's happily ever after right? It might it seems like it has been you made
very happy
Periods of your life is it is it still or is this?
feeling in the past, but I do see like so next we have the three of cups and three of cups is like sometimes a third party situation
But it's like people celebrating usually the celebrations card
So maybe also I see this looks like a kind of a team
So maybe some of you yeah, you work with and somebody else coming together
And
Vampire
And she used to like, you know, stalk James Dean and actually refused her.
It is the Empire, I think.
Either way.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Okay, so give her a readings act to it so far.
Carry on.
Okay.
And then we have this, I mean, my glasses, we have this, okay, the Ace of Wands.
Ace of Wands is like some kind of new thing handed to you that's going to be really passionate about.
This one says, a spiritual gift ideas flow towards your soul.
Follow your passion.
High potential for growth.
Beware of pitfalls.
So there's the...
Okay, okay.
Carry on.
Okay, next we have, okay we have the Six of Pentacles. This is like, uh, this, this is
the spirit of charity, right? And it's like, I think it might be like, you know, the night
before Christmas or something, or it's kind of like, some kind of scary ghost, like, uh,
dropping these like, uh, these coins, but it says the Six of Pentacles, the spirit of charity.
type of material abundance where it's like you are able to, you know, give to charity and give
note to the causes that you want to support as you wish. And it's like, and it's just saying you should be doing this,
but continue and do that, but also, you know,
measure who you give to and make sure they are worthy of it, you know.
For you, okay, and let's see what else we have.
Queen of Swords
So an unbiased tale of independence. Okay, and so this is a very independent woman. I don't know if this I don't
Are you married or I'm not sure if you're heterosexual or homosexual just zero comment on that one, but yeah
Okay, but this is like, I guess an air sign woman,
and so if this woman is in your life already,
I don't know if you're dating somebody,
or if you're married or whatever.
It's not in my business, but it's like,
this is like, she'd divorcee or something, though.
I don't know.
Queens and Swords usually are,
they're also really good with words.
Sometimes it's a little bit fighting with them,
but everything's been in the upright,
I'll pull up a couple more.
Okay, we also have this Eight of Pentacles.
This says it's the Apprentice,
so maybe like teaching somebody,
trade but in this card. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, well, it's like it's like you got that you got that queen of swords
Then you got this suit this this five of swords and it's like so that makes you think maybe you're gonna have
Like she she'd like took some guys head off or something like that like right so I think yeah, it says brutal
brutal victory, you know, and so it's like
The five of swords, you know, it's like there's a victory for somebody and there's yeah
I can I can take a reading from it. So last card. Come on. Okay. The last card is gonna be
The two of pentacles. This is gonna be trying to save balance
It says the two of pentacles a journey into equilibrium, you know
No matter what if even if the world's fire behind you, you know, you're gonna want to like save balance
I'll take the reading. It's a positive one. It's very, yeah, it makes sense to everything.
And it's so stupid to me that it all makes sense. And I know it's just a parlor trick
and anyone can do it.
What do you mean parlor trick? A parlor trick is when I actually would have like talent
and shuffling and like, no, no, it's just
It's it's very vague
It's what I don't want to tell you like you know because Chris K will come here
I'm not gonna say anything bad about Chris K, but Chris K will be like
Oh, is it was your mother's like names are with a C and it's like what's the D?
I mean, it's like I'm not gonna play a guessing game with anybody about it. It's like probably not a bet
That's not the most important thing. I'm not gonna try to get all this
Perfectly detailed information. I'm gonna like feel and like you're feeling for the message
And it's like it all here. I just think that like my point, dude
Is that every single card in that deck is going to mean something to someone right right because every deck is an archetype
And we are full of these archetypes and so
each of them will represent some time of our life or something that will happen
of somewhere. It's irrelevant in which or do you pull them
it's always going to mean something to someone. Right.
Right, there's no magic. There's no spirituality behind it. There's no juju. There's no
It's just a parlor trick that some people fall for and they think it's
Paranormal okay, you don't have to believe it. I do like stop
Paranormal the tarot show do everybody say it's paranormal. I'm saying I
you know, float in the air and stuff like that I'm saying, that I can like, you know, understand symbolism and people's emotions and, you know...
but your stream name is sorcery magic and haunted panel
now that would suggest the realms of the paranormal to me
I explain but why is there's like there's nobody here I guess I scared them away
I was gonna say ghost ghost sky ghost wanted me to name the panel after that
So, by then, it's...
Well, maybe kind of rename it a second now.
Now that is in your brain.
Name it what?
I don't know, huh? Whatever you said it was.
I don't care. I mean, it's almost Halloween, right?
Oh, well.
It's almost Halloween. It's almost Christmas.
It's almost fucking it. It's almost next January. It's almost
Everyone was everyone was trying to play like, you know, white Christmas yesterday. I was like, guys, you don't play Christmas songs in August
I think it's bad luck or like, you know, it's you know, it's really really mad when you do that
Like he doesn't want he's tired trying to sleep and he doesn't like to be woke up with Christmas songs in the middle of August
right
What was the channel's MC to subscribe yet? Or we go ahead and
I love, if KZ wants a full body massage from Psyche, I will concur.
So J-Dog, you're saying I can, you're saying I, you want to do a full body massage, J-Dog
with me?
Well, Psyche has all been a bit crazy.
I want to thank you very much for the, for greeting.
Oh, you're welcome.
Hey, you're welcome.
I think I'm gonna leave you here in peace and let you chill out with your chat wonderful people
No, no, no fucking um, I forget which meltdown I saw you in
There's always a meltdown on that fucking channel
Yeah, yeah, like if you can honestly pinpoint what fucking meltdown it was I don't know
I'll always say they to you if I see you in the chat there
Are you there a lot?
Wait, I don't know.
God bless, everyone.
Fucking stay safe.
Don't check out the Trials on Lemon Show.
You can check it out on YouTube.
You can check it out on Rumble if you're an ex-user
and you want to see the fucking depravity that
is this planet.
Check out Trials on X. Other than that, god bless, everyone.
Sight stay safe.
And thanks for having me out.
Thank you, my friend.
No, yes, they say if everyone you away
Appreciate you brother catch you next time. You too come back soon. I will do man. I will do ladies
Yeah, I mean it's like it's hard guys, it's like, you know, that's why it's hard to do free reading sometimes because I
It's like
Not only did he like not
He was kind of respectful to that, but it's like how about at least like respectful, I don't know.
Anyhow, what am I doing? Okay, so I'm looking maybe for something.
But it's that subway right now.
that's the problem. Let's see. Oh, no problem. You're fine. Yeah, go ahead and subscribe to
the Trials and Limit of mods who get his link or something. I'm not sure. I bet you can't.
yeah okay guys we have some exciting stuff happening I am actually getting
like some attention from other other platforms and exciting stuff like it's
just like when people are asking and wanting to
I'm part of the show, I've had these appearances with Alexandra Mayer, she's great, you have
to check out her channel, Alexandra Mayer, I think her other channel, I mean her other
channel is still up I believe, the links are both on my, on my community page for all her
channels.
Alexandra, M-A-Y-E-R, at Alexandra Mayor. She does some Bible reading, really cool. I think
that's a really cool practice, is to go through the whole Bible and read the whole thing. I did
that with the first five books, which is like the Torah, and I studied them in a
The interbreed between the lines and a lot of things when you look like he's so cherished you use them, right?
Yeah, it's interesting it is about light very
very nice me
Kind of steady so as much Buddhism
Yeah, that means psychies also. Yep, I do channel too
Let's see, okay, thank you. I need to put my glasses down
Do you see tricks over there? There's tricks in the alien cat. Hi tricks. Hey, there's Rudy up where you just looked up there
And Mr. Trixie
Hi guys, how are you doing?
I'm gonna like probably, I'm gonna try to get a green screen, I guess, for up here in the green screen, and then I'll fix it when I do stuff like this.
Which is like, I can now do really cool things.
Do you guys, are you guys down to like, watch some classic moments? Cause it's like, there's nobody here, I guess.
I don't know if anybody sees that I'm live, or they just hate them.
The name of it, but that's fine.
Because I think I'll be attracting new people too.
Okay, so let's see.
I have to...
I might want to watch.
Oh yeah, my old show. Okay, so let me see.
Please stand by.
Okay.
What's up, guys?
I'm back.
I'm back. I just had a really good dinner.
Wow, it was a really awesome dinner.
I had a cocktail called the OG, I think it was called.
The OG.
I had tequila.
I had pineapple.
And lime and watermelon.
Kind of like my drinks. I'm drinking tonight. My come kombucha. I'm having hard kombucha. I have like probably two left. I
Don't know
But I have a cheesecake. Let's look at my first guest tonight
If I need to put up the let me see I was going slow the second look I'm Joker TV
And for Janet, it's going to be really slow.
I'm sorry, bear with me.
Guys, we're going to have fun tonight.
Oh, hold on.
I'm going to mute him instead of putting it.
I'm going to be muted.
I'm trying to.
There you go.
Joker.
Janet.
Joker come back
My fucking it's going so slow. I'm sorry. There you go
Can you hear me
Yeah, yeah, hello darling
I hear you can hear me yes, okay, but oh girl. What's up? What's up?
How are you?
I'm good. I'm good. So listen. How was your dinner?
It was really good. It was really good
Like I'll tell the story again like she came over
She was at my door as soon as I ended my stream. She was at the door
This is Rudy's mom. She's a family friend. I got Rudy, Rudy from and she came in
we called Rudy for a few minutes and
Rudy wasn't coming out and then Trix was coming over
No, Casey, I'm already mod you. Casey you're fine. The reason I modded everybody, okay?
I didn't know for anything personal. I'll add you as a mom. I
Said I don't know sometimes I don't know who I can trust right?
I'm gonna knock on my door you're modding in case you know. Yeah, nothing personal
I was like cuz I had a lot of troll mods that I had and I so I didn't know who to trust it's up
Okay, so let's welcome our another guest
You've been waiting for you
So Jamie Rose was up girl guys. It's a party tonight
Empress Janet and Jamie Rose and gosh. Oh, yeah, you're gonna have some fun tonight
What happened with your dinner, my girl?
I went to dinner and I'll tell you,
so she came over and then Rudy,
and then she, I was like, okay, Rudy's under the bed
and come over and say hi, come over
and get Rudy out from under the bed.
Okay, Michael's here.
That's where it's a party tonight.
Okay.
who's this guy? He's the guy that was blowing kisses on the other panel so I know that psych is
gonna love him. Hey, he was literally blowing kisses to guys on the other panel site so
yeah he doesn't like us. He likes to use women for money and then fuck men so we get it.
Yeah, it's a story.
Gay for straight.
Look, though.
Look, it's like...
You know, I didn't find any glory holes for you, bro.
But again, there's a lot of them that we're sitting on the panel
asking about your party.
And I told them...
No, it's not going to be a glory hole.
It's my girl's mouth.
And they're not going to share their glory holes.
Definitely don't want to put my dick in your mouth.
Like just working for people with city bodies,
oil parties, and again I have no interest in that.
He taught me father, do you know what I mean Frank?
Why would I be arguing with a gay man? I have no reason to do it.
I'm going to go up mute because I don't need to argue with him.
He wants to blow kisses at you, say.
Yeah, the next time you do anything that what you mentioned my girl is my girl mouth
Like where you mentioned anything about me and Tracy and my girl
That's it.
Somebody talk.
It's like, I can't hear anything.
It's done.
I don't hear anything.
They can't be bothered to irrelevant people that don't exist.
They sure don't exist.
They don't exist.
I know this panel literally was on the panel.
Blowing kisses at Joker.
I think, I think, yeah.
Well, it was a joke.
Hello.
I'll go on mute. Thank you, Jamie for having a pussy. Say hello. It was a joke. Hello
That's what you said
He was blowing kisses to another man on the panel not the women
But she don't need to worry about us
They close the fucking
Can you talk with the we're basing your voice I can hear the fucking doors so I can be up on this gay man's panel
Get my rocks off trying to go after women that could never
Okay, I can't be bothered. It's like a little raw fish trying to, wants us to catch it and throw it back, you know what I mean?
Very little. Yeah, we'd rather get some glory holes because Betta was supposed to come over. She was supposed to stop the show. Come on over.
She's coming. She's coming right now.
Cheating on me. Well, hold on. Where the breasts at?
Sike, I tried to bring all the glory holes to you. They're on their way
People are here
Fucking cunt bitch
You fucking all you did was fucking cheat on me all night long you fucking take your ass everywhere
You left my panel without saying bye you fucking went out groovy jimmy
This fucking relationship is over. I just came up here to say that. I don't want to talk to you anymore
I'm watching you. Don't ever call me again
Wow
Or
Hard kaboosh. I'm gonna go cry. I'll be right back. Thank you
Don't you dare. You're not allowed to cry. It's my turn to cry. Fuck you
So all the glory hoes are here for you psych and um me and beta are and jamie have pussy. So we're going on mute
No, y'all got to get naked. Yeah. Yeah
We were to promise some lingerie
We hear for the ladies we hear for the for the for the booty
for the boobies. You said booty, Freudian. Yeah, the booty. Yeah, the booty. We want that booty.
You said booty hole. I heard you. I actually know about no booty hole, but... I heard you.
We all heard you. Who's on stage? Show your...
All right, but you go first. Winged shuttle. Winged shuttle. They can't see you.
I'm spreading my wings and this is the show for you heard
Such an immature channel
Crazy. Yeah, really? Yeah, truly. Oh my god. I need my where is my
Is that paycheck Dave that's
Hey, Dave
Okay, I'll do it. I'll show tits first every if I showed tits where everyone else showed it
but
If you do that first Jamie, I swear to God, I will do it. All right, okay, I'll get the party started home
Okay, you do it first
Okay
You know what you don't know full-screen though. Okay, she's doing it awful skin don't know don't full-screen. You just
I won't I'll put you center-stage
No, it's all black
That's what
Now what now we ain't nothing it's for toots. We didn't see nothing
All we saw was black screen Jamie
That's where Jamie it was it's just a black screen
Oh my God. Oh my God. You're lying. You're lying. There you go,
psych. You know, there's a movie to it. Yeah, you did it. Oh my God. Damn, Jamie. How many more are
you gonna have open up?
Yeah, am I in the show right now? Hello? Is this thing on? Hello? I'm trying to call out nobody. I'm in the show. Welcome to the, I can't see. Oh, there's that guy. There's that buffalo guy.
Jamie
Muslim guy, I think that's a chick. There's a girl right there next to him. Who's the chick telling tell her to put her on camera
She don't want to call her right now.
She's all alone.
No, not on camera.
And yeah, even that guy on camera, yeah, it makes me sick.
It makes me want to kill you.
J-Doc, are you there?
So, J-Doc, are you there?
And Groovy, Jim, are you there?
Or else I have to take you off.
So everybody's gone.
No, no, no, we're here.
We're here.
There's so many backstage, your name is N-I-G-C-A-M-A-M.
Do I look, do you even know this person?
No.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's, that's Uncle Scam.
We know him.
Oh!
I'm gonna do with this.
Do I let him on?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you can go.
What's up, Scam?
That's Scam.
Yeah
For a second look. Yeah, look he ran
Said that yeah, who said that? It was not me. It was me. I said that
Who said that?
I know, right?
Yeah, who said that?
We're all thinking it.
I just checked the log.
He can't make this shit up.
No, he can't make this shit up.
This is crazy work right here.
They all want your glory all touched.
Oh my god, hey, who's this asshole from super bad next. Oh, it's
Oh, my God.
We have a full panel tonight.
We have a full panel.
Have I met maximum people on the panel?
No, not tonight.
When everyone is on camera, then it'll be full.
This is not a full panel.
OK?
Who is that?
Who is he?
Panel full.
They call somebody else a dumb bitch.
You dumb bitch.
Not even.
Not even Groovy Jimmy's willing to come up
on your fucking gas panel, dude.
I
Mean as a homosexual man, you got a real gay panel going on
Yes
Like when you call me that name I like it
Talk dirty talk dirty to me keep going
you you pussy you pussy uh you uh show your feet show your feet show your feet pussy square
can you show your feet let's go
bet you his toes nails are yellow as fuck
i don't know
probably if i need to clip them either
What's that first Janet doing I want to see ever is Janet back some set up man like last time I seen this she was on a
behind the scenes
Yeah, Janet will you go behind the scenes with me next? God damn
Jamie again, can you show your your tie-dye stuff?
Yeah
Yeah, we need to get a party started.
Are you there, Janet?
Janet's not there.
Show feet.
Fuck you, Janet. Fuck you.
Okay, Bita. Bita, can I show you what I got tonight?
Where's mom brought me something?
Janet was like the biggest bitch.
She cheated on me all night tonight.
Bita, you're disgusting.
Bita, look at it.
Where's mom brought me this?
Biji, you can suck my Buddha.
What is that?
Bita, can you see?
Can you see?
Oh.
No
We're trying to get in
Discussing assholes with no cameras. It shouldn't even be a question. Start kicking motherfuckers
that
Simply lemonade simply scissor
Start with Jimmy look Jimmy. Okay start with the people that always come up if you're always cammed up and you're not willing to come up here
You're gone Jimmy start with Jimmy. That's a great
I
Everyone in the chat says kick Jimmy
People off, but you can come back and stuff like that. You're not talking and it's like I'm having a lot of people trying to come in and stuff
You can come back and stuff like that
You can't you can't right you're okay cut rude desktop any other
Oh
Yeah, any other young bows any other young there you go one of any other cameras on
Yeah, yeah, young bucks up to the chat young bucks young bucks to the front
Good morning guys. Oh my god. Hold on. Janet. Is that you?
Why do you look like that?
That's definitely. Janet looks fucking fierce. She looks like her.
You're on like, you're in a k-hole right now, Janet.
Janet looks amazing. She's a doll.
My darling. Look at her. Look at her. She looks amazing. Why are there people on? She's smoking a cig.
He didn't just broke up with me.
He's Hollywood time, yeah.
You showed your ass when you did that.
Janet, did you forget?
Backstage, remember when you did that?
Dude, I have no clue what's going on.
You guys have no coordination.
Janet showed her asshole backstage to Bita,
and now Janet doesn't want to talk.
Now Janet's acting like she didn't do it, like you're
Sixty teeth Janet. Hey Janet one thing. I clipped
Clips don't like no girl. That's transsexual
I'm not like how it was already half a blurred out like it should be
Yeah, well, you're not watching.
Look at the chitter on that critter.
the
Looks good
There's so many
Nobody likes you guys on no cameras
Yeah, no cameras. Oh, we got beta over here, and then the home girl fucking
That's a 40 year old man with a fake
Your camera, it's your feet
I'm sorry if I kicked anybody out of the studio that was anticipating you guys are welcome back
It's just like too crazy tonight. The people are trying to get in the studio
57 people in the studio. This is my maximum people ever had in my chat in the studio. I'm trying to do my best
Hey
Michael yeah, okay. Hey, what up Michael who's got a bigger forehead you're your girl
Is that what you got the fucking beanie on the like cover your forehead?
I think I think I have a bigger forehead, but it's nice
You got to take the message off the screen
Oh
Like already blocked her girl with the fucking image right there
knows this guy
Why are you against me? I think you're on mushrooms again. You need to chill the fuck out though. Dude, imagine not taking mushrooms
That's a fucking gay dog guys assaulting
This dog is happy that dog is a happy dog. What a sweet dog. Oh
Who was taking care of that dog when you were roaming the streets for weeks and months on end Joker?
I think that about you BG so you want to say that stuff about me too
Don't say anything bad about my girl you could talk all this shit you want about me
But keep my fucking girl's name out your fucking mouth.
I don't give a fuck.
You can talk all this shit you want about me.
Don't fucking be talking shit about my girl, bro.
Who's talking shit about your girl?
Don't be talking shit about me.
We can't see Jamie.
Oh, hey, there is Jamie.
There's a cat.
We can work here.
Oh, man.
Jamie, what's up?
This is the first time I've seen ever.
I've never seen Jamie Rose on Cam.
Cam done before.
Damn, okay.
What up, Jamie?
Yeah.
What up?
Yeah, who's talking about that shit?
It's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me
parent teacher conference, okay? We don't need you. Yeah, you would bring your little to work. Okay. Hey,
Jamie, you're matching other people, but you're not used to getting matched.
Jamie, I have two inches ready for you. Um, I don't want them. I'm good. Hey, nobody's lonely.
I'm the only one here.
What the fuck are you talking about BG?
Yeah, I'm your only one here.
I'm not sure he's broke.
Obviously, I'm not sure.
You know what you're trying to do?
And after this, I'm going to let it go.
Because I know you're trying to get on my bad side.
Even though I never did anything wrong to you BG.
I even subscribe to your channel.
Like the video with BG.
BG.
Benny beating up his mom and dad, why would you like that? You enjoy that content?
Yeah, yeah, I actually do. Yeah, he's approved that very beat his mom up. Oh, yeah
Yeah, so why the fuck you're gonna go against me? I didn't do anything wrong to you
I never did
Jokes are
When it comes to my girlfriend
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done
I
Imprisoned they put serpents
I bet hey, alright. I'll say this right now. I wasn't trying to diss you if you took it that way
I can see why and my bad. I'm not trying to diss you
Alright peace out
Hey, it was a distasteful joke and my jokes aren't for everybody my bad that it was in your expense
Anyway
I don't I want to hear from i got a and I got nothing right. I'm glad you and your girl are together
So look if you're happy if you guys was happy then
Hey Salus man, she my abs dude. Thank you. I see oh wow
Yeah
Let's see the
You like to take advantage people who are on disability. Oh, okay. Who said that? Who said that?
Is it this guy, Wayne finder, Wayne finder said that, or BG, who said that, BG or Wayne finder?
Wayne, watch that, Wayne.
Why, why is it insane?
Oh, he's gone, all right.
That's funny.
Can you hear me?
That is definitely not a six-five.
What is that, Booker?
What is that?
A six-five, dude.
Thank you.
Yeah, six pack of pills.
Yes.
It's my favorite show.
Me and Jamie, I'm pregnant with Jamie's baby.
Okay, the chat says you need to get a Sharpie.
Get a Sharpie six pack.
Get a Sharpie, Joker.
You all are all pregnant with me.
Mm-hmm.
The if this dude was not making fucking what are they called taco rolls will ever fuck they are nasty
That's a nasty. You should have ever seen in my life
That's some trailer parts
What's it called a taco
Taco roll
With a sharpie are you sure he's done the fucking
Oh, no permanent doing a Mickey Mouse face on
Put a smile face. Are you sure?
No, nothing's wrong with no Totino's pizza rolls. Totino's is fine, but this guy took a whole Crescent roll
Took some taco meat that he completely burned number one completely burned
Put that in a in a fucking Crescent roll, right? Then he wrapped it up. He's drawing with this crippled hand, by the way
Okay
I guess. Keep going, Joker. Keep going.
Put some, like, make it mad, though. Make it, make it, make it, put some swirly.
Don't take too fast. It looks like BG.
Oh, okay. Give it some bald. Why is it bald, though, you know what I mean?
Give it some hair. You know what I mean? You know what I mean? You know what I mean?
Don't don't charge yourself homie
With a strong pain. Yeah. Yeah, thank you for the air. Okay. Yep
Looks like a Barbie doll
It looks like said from fucking Toy Story. Thank you good officer
This is hot yeah, put a beard put a chin strap give it a Jimmy chin strap
Full gym
A little lower make a beard
Okay, I don't know guys I'm gonna try to bring more people up in a second because I don't when I'm like go off of a joker
Yeah, I like I like this. Oh, yeah
I want to lick that off of you.
What do you like about this?
He wants to lick it.
Well, could you keep doing with a full chin strap?
Definitely.
A full Amish chin strap, like an Amish person.
Like an Amish man, a full chin strap.
No, a chin strap.
Turns to a full goatee when he pulls out his pants a little bit.
I need to know you guys.
I know you all add you to the show, but if I don't know you,
I have to wait a little bit, OK?
And then can you put like a, like a, like a little mustache, like a, like a retard that can't grow a mustache, like kind of can, like a little bit.
I was about to say, yeah, okay, make it blackfish.
Can I see your nipples?
Can you make like, you make antennas with the nipples and like attach them to your nipples, like with antennas?
Okay, okay. Oh wait, oh wait
No, I was throwing the ones Jimmy had no one
Thank you Joker. Thank you Joker. He was bouncing around.
That was you.
He sure was.
Hey, Michael, this is why you don't have fucking kids.
You're just so conscious of it.
People like Joker, dude.
Well, probably. Who knows?
I feel sad for Michael and his girlfriend.
They're just like watching this.
You feel sad for me and my girlfriend?
I feel bad for Michael's girlfriend.
Michael is subjecting his girlfriend to this.
If it wasn't for Michael, his girlfriend would be gone.
Oh yeah, all right, that's true, that's true.
This is really hard to do.
All right, EG, you're right about that.
What's your movie, bro?
What's your fucking movie?
This is so-
Hey, Mizer, what's up, Mizer?
Mizer, it's going crazy over here.
I don't know what's going on.
Look at me, sir.
Mizer, look.
Oh my god.
Oh, no.
Oh, okay.
My big belly, get my belly, get my belly.
Right.
Pull up a little bit more, Joker.
Just a little bit more.
Can you roll your belly?
I don't know what I can do anymore. I don't even know what's going
Joker thinks he's artistic
He does artist he does
He does right. What do you call it like art like he draws he draws
He draws
He's like an artist
I love it
Joker got hit by a parked car now, let William see it. Hey guys. Oh, you remember that BG what he got?
Does anyone know this guy William C? Is this guy William C okay or no?
Is William C okay or no? Hold on
I'm gonna ban her for one second. I just want to see if this guy's okay
This guy's trying to fuck me over. He's he's done. Okay. Hold on. Not even over this guy
To nigger island
No, it's on the chat let him up and stuff. I mean a bit of
Don't sing that song
To nigger island
Jamie!
because he didn't
That was a live performance. That was not live night
All right, you know what just do you let them let them on again BG saves you BG just saved you did
Not letting that guy back on again. I'm not letting that guy back on again
Yeah, they just copy his name
Any asshole could have done that
BG is smart, he is like 5 IQ.
But he he's a great you should let bill up bill is very fun
Oh, yeah, that was definitely bill if you're gonna let bill up put the blocker up and then let him do his for live performance
You know
It's an audio bomb. It's I can't have a song it's trying to
I rep them another song from Howard Stern Joker. I want to see the nipples though. I want to see it making my antennas
What? I don't want to see him.
Stop.
You're fine. You're fine.
Oh, let me rejoin.
Okay.
You know what? Don't come back.
Jamie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'd rather see Jamie.
Jamie.
What's your opinion on me, my new girlfriend?
Who's your girlfriend?
It might be my piece of shit.
Calm down, Ian.
Who's your girlfriend?
The one I'm next to.
Thought we're not allowed to have hold on. I thought we weren't allowed to have opinions. Well, can she talk I mean
She's out of your league dude, she needs to break up with you she's out of your
I don't even know enough about life yet.
Anybody doesn't know anything about life.
So where did you meet her?
The methadone miles?
Never listen to that way of keeping up.
I'm sorry.
I'm muting.
I did, actually.
I don't mean to make a horseman wait. Why are you my discord? I know I know the song
I know I know Howard Stern. I know the song
I know I know every like racist redneck fucking song in the world. Okay guys, you're not gonna fool me
I knew that song instantly. I've heard that song. Okay. I even might have laughed one the time
Which I thought the song is not for the show
Not approving my show. Okay, so everyone that's saying to let him up because you're trying to get me in trouble and stuff
I'm gonna be
You're in trouble for the 24 hours, okay?
I'm not trying to get you in trouble.
Okay
Jamie you co-wrote that song someone's like you co-wrote that song. You should only let people on you know and people
Great song. I know
Now what now I will tonight tonight. It's a special. It's my it's a it's a VIP only diddy party
If I don't know your ass then you're welcome on the panel, right? I know Joker and again
So I know BG. I know Michael. I know Jamie. So you guys are all good not anybody on that. I don't know, okay?
And I'm going to put a brick wall up anyway to make sure I do know you and you're not using some phony photo
Like using a fake picture of beat and stuff
Or things like that, right? I'm smarter. I got I'm getting smarter and wiser. Okay. I'm gonna get to this ship
Jen has some name on here. Why don't you kick her off with the phone?
She's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore, she's not even talking anymore
Oh shit
It should be like a thing I'm gonna show like some lube hang on
I got mine right here psych
Shuffle the deck, breathe in the flame
The answers are near, just whisper his name
Got it
watch and tell it.
So, maybe we can all watch these reviews and see, you know, I got a decent Aurora Borealis
lamp for six bucks. The, yeah, remote stop working for it. Hi, guys. Oh, yeah. This came from Timo
today. I just ordered this the other day. Hey, Boston, how are you? Boston's the member. Welcome,
Boston. Hey, Jamie. Yeah, so I got this from Timo. It's actually from, you know, the third party
I took your wrench up
Backbarber
Yeah, I got your back. Hold on but I want to do this for I have to go into my
to go into my
Sitting on the case those little kids
Okay, it's a little nice. Okay. This was like five ten bucks. I don't know it was
Okay, so it's a little bit
Okay, look
It's got a lot of stuff in it. It's cool. I like the colors red and black
guys, I have
Nail cleaners to my my heart's delight, right?
Got some clippers. I got you know, it's like doesn't feel like the most
Expensive you know, they feel kind of that some of them feel plastic. Yeah, but
Hi hi guys, hey
How do you do this guys? Yeah, it's very nice. And so I got a little
It's just has this little cleaner. So I just always scrape out my nails
Look, they'll probably be better than they've ever ever been in a while
And I guess so yeah, it takes it right out
Amazing sometimes we have problems for such a long time and then it's like it's just it has a simple fix
Right so always look out for this
Best solution sometimes there's called hacks
Okay, I mean, it's like dinner. It's not like wow. I mean, it's like it's kind of getting and you really need to scrape up there
Oh, yeah, I think a lot of it up
The headaches are your headaches are
At baby, oh my headsets are rocking
Crackling me crackling. I'm sorry. Yeah, see hello
Testing up how does that guy is that better? Okay, I think it was too close to my mouth. So there we are that better
testing one two three calling will Robinson hmm how's your day guys I got
some rest today a little bit to eat that's a start drinking a little bit
dirt but it's like not super fast. I don't know. I had to entertain myself on that right tool for
this deal. So this is the one I'm using right now. So this is like a tiny spoon. I mean it's like
guys I mean it's like it's like 100 cokes spoons or something. What is this one? Okay so there's one of the
Okay, oh gosh, I guess we got some good stuff though. I can clean out my other pipe too with some of this stuff
Okay, it's a little cool little guys. It was they know for six bucks a team who?
Delivered, you know
The light too. That's like just cool cheap stuff. I would I would maybe take out
some of the more
Expenses that they have on there because maybe you're gonna get you know, I don't I got me
Hit phones all the battery. I got some saves tonight. We can get all the energy clear
I did kind of burn myself less than it was a sage
That wasn't great, but guys
Yeah, they're all negative energy is collecting smoke and then go out the window be dispelled
Be dispelled turn to this sender any negative energy
ain't sent to me or
Any of the kind-hearted people in the chat
Okay, and we have the power we do have the power to bless
So we have the power to bless where we are we have the power to the curse where we are to you I suppose right so
how about
We learn about blessings and you said conscious blessings when we enter we enter a place, you know and
to our own homes and to all our inhabitants and to everyone in our life
So
Noble are you?
Yeah, so we can invoke these blessings. Wow here we go guys look at all the smoke
Sometimes you can see interesting stuff in the smoke if you look back. I don't know
Maybe just see some hello Vader. How are you?
It says it's really effective. I do think it's super effective
And I'm pulling out some of the negative energy
I know it's been probably used for thousands of years and it has a very very distinctive and lovely smell
Hey Jamie or hey Vader
It is a little sparky
Thank you, I want to get a demon out of
How do we do that in cards?
Well, I wouldn't say a card would do an exorcism.
I'd say the cards, they can be used in conjunction with that.
I would say certainly perform a reading before you do any exorcism
or any other kind of magical working.
See what the energies are like and how things are likely to turn out.
See, just give that idea of a feel for the energy when you're about to do something like that.
Um, you know, I think I also think it's a very kind of this kind of judgment. So when we're like, oh, this person's demon possesses
it's like
Okay, maybe maybe even possessed. Maybe
They're possessive themselves. Maybe yeah, there's the ego is in total control of the the onima, right?
so
So when we say, oh, they're being possessed, you know, I think it's I think I'm not gonna ever go around my life and say
I oh, I rebuke you and then no call a woman something like Jezebel or something like that. Oh, and that's not that's not
That's not about like what I'm about, right?
It's like that some people will say oh, yeah, go do that go perform exorcism
Some people have tied people down into the beds and you know, there's horrible stories that Emily Rose case is based on a true story
Look into the true story of Emily Rose. It's just very sad stuff, you know, some of it might be
Some of it might be
You know mental illness, so it might be
Different drugs or some kind of poisoning or something like that
Some it could be just the religious poisoning that religious mind can hope that's how it does drive some people nuts
You know, because you start believing in devils and angels and
Sometimes you'll take it
A little bit too literally working on salvation with fear and tremble. Yeah. Well, I also think that it's like
There's like perfect love and perfect trust, right?
And it's like, you know, we can fear God ultimately we should I mean you can see ultimately God is in control of everything, right?
but
Just it's like kind of like
Do your parents want to be loved or feared by maybe a little bit of both maybe like a little bit about okay
You'll behave yourself better if you fear, but you know, I basically don't know, you know that we're loving the benevolent forces, right?
I think that's similar to God
We'd love this so much that he gave us free will
So Ziggy what do you see what what where's my dick fix the
I'm getting sick of this shit, okay? Always sending it to other people
Telling me I'm bothering you when I asked for it. You be flatter
Okay, so there we go, that's okay. Oh, that's okay. That was a message that even Emily Rose wanted to send out
Yeah, the message is
Um, can I handle that? Um, handle, but they use those message, uh, that Emily Rose would want to just send out and handle that. Tell your friend, Russ, that's your friend, Russ is your friend, isn't she? I mean, she's my friend, too, but, you know, she's kind of new to the show. I think she was hanging out with your group, guys.
Her name is uh, I think uh panel panel boots or something that in the chat
And how to say too much of me. I did talk to her. I just
Yeah
Yeah, he's not on the please not on he's not on the blog list. He's just he might be or he or she they might be
timed out
24 hours probably back a lot of people like are already time already time back in before they are
Asking about it. It's like go test it, you know, I used to
I just some two conclusions sometimes but
Me when people assume it just makes it ask out of you and me
Um, I can do it. I can do it, but yeah, and let's see. I sent her a dick pic like five years ago. Okay
Well, you know, you look you look you look you look you look great. You look just look great, you know
What happened these last five years? You have a tough. You know, I have one last five months. So imagine having
to mod it imagine being a mod and
sends you a
Deepic I
Got it every day. Oh
My gosh, I get it
Oh
Are you complaining about that
Well, I don't even know is that a big issue guys. Oh my gosh
You dick every day. I don't really have more dick than me. It's boobs. I mean women aren't just like sending out pictures of boobs like willy-nilly
It's like, you know, you know, you at least have a girl's gone wild t-shirt and you know
Pity bucks or a hundred bucks or something. I don't know but that's the minimum
It's gonna send send it out to strangers on the internet
They're fake photos
Ladies don't do it. Don't do it. I know we had a problem. Oh issue somebody
You can send guys are sticking they do revenge porn and it's one sort of post
A picture of somebody I know. We all know they're on the show last night.
And uh, my mic okay? I'll check one too.
Maybe I'm just talking, or hold on, am I holding these?
I need to put these down, maybe,
because I think that maybe is the,
maybe is crackling.
You're shixie.
Hi, wait.
So how do you have a couple of my drinks tonight?
You don't do revenge for it?
I know it's, not only is it illegal,
but it's like, you know.
Just low it's saying that nobody really care. I mean, it's like I don't think people really care except for the person that it's
doing it too. It's really it's really
really I mean
destroyed a lot of people even people have AI fake AI porn and
Come to showing people and upsetting people with and people are jumping to conclusions about it
So
There's always doing it rusty and you had it's truth, but okay. Well
Guys you need to truce up again. Okay, I can't have my you know people fighting in my chat
See you uh
Too sad, okay
So Dean, let me see. Oh, it's only personalized my phone
Okay little themes, okay
i think i'll do c way by the c so it says rest okay so it says cb if i send you a pick
would you be mad i would be mad because i mean i mean i know you asked somebody else but i mean
personally i would be mad i would be you know i would say finally he sent it you know i've been
some people wait a lifetime for a picture like this. Some people last forever for
that one special kiss. Oh, I'm sorry, my own life. Oh my gosh. I apologize. Yeah, no
anyone's, no anyone's dick. I mean, dick's are kind of weird to like, especially the women.
I mean, I think they look pretty cool, but it's like
Sometimes they look funny
They're common all shapes inside of like balloon animals, right?
Just like the pictures of a region team and a family we've all seen lately. Those are not I don't think those are real pictures
You love the channel, thank you Phyllis. Thank you so much. I appreciate you. I
Love you
Okay, I love you guys so much.
Let me see.
System control vibration, and this phone has more settings
than the Apollo 13.
Okay, let's see.
Hey, fellas, thank you guys.
Yeah, guys, the channel is also doing well.
I have a membership.
I would love you guys to join the membership.
It's so cool.
I love seeing the names in the chat, it will be easier to see who's the member in the chat, anybody?
We got Barbara, Barbara's a member.
Barbara and I think Barbara's the only one in the chat right now, but we do have almost over 70, so
probably shout out to the members, I will always try to give members a shout out.
No time
Even though Charles Manson wrote that song, but he turns out you wrote some other other Beach Boys song or something, but
Yeah
Yeah, dude, dude, dude, dude, it sounds like Sesame Street, right?
Hi, yeah, it's a good song
I mean, it's one of the classic songs of all time, but it is, you know, the Beatles didn't just come out of nowhere
They just, well, let's start a band, you know, and make music. It was kind of an idea
floating around for a while
Finally able to take it to on TV turn it turns magic really young full blast, right? I can't play it but I can sing it
I don't know. I'm not sure the other words. I don't know. I'm sorry. They were a subpar
boy band. Yeah, but they were one of the first and also they were, you know, I think they're
probably one of the first, you know, there's a place called the Tavistock Institute. It's
And it is where, you know, there's a think tank, a think tank where, you know, a lot of ideas are thrown around and maybe instituted into the mainstream, right?
I can't say too much about it, but, you know, you can look into it.
A lot of the world as we know it today is fake.
Um, programmed controlled mind control. I don't know how to put it, you know, it's like that, you know
There's something going on, right?
So like there's really cool books available on amazon for free guys
You can go to amazon and try to search or like you say like search for zero
like for like zero
Um, I think they're called zero because there's a lot of ones that are free. Let's say
The whole section I think of the ebooks that are free. I got thousands of them on my
Am I out of my abs? Who is tonight? What's wrong?
Maybe it was wrong. It's from the night minutes. Thanks bad things we go
What are we gonna do guys? Okay, so
I do have thousands of books. I can read cool stuff, you know
I'm just looking for
Something that kind of be enjoyed by the whole chat, right?
Okay
Lot of stuff. I've read a lot of self-help book a lot of the cults books a lot of
books on tarot
Okay, so maybe this will I'll find me a fine one that was just resonate somehow you see
And bear with me guys are thousands of them books
Okay, we can look at the origin of names, words, everything in between.
What does it bother saying?
Definitely you're going to have to gather more rock songs.
Yeah, maybe in my other channel.
Okay, so this is about, this is called the origin of names, words, and everything in between.
Okay.
Okay, so it's just countries. Okay, so if you're reading this on a boat, a plane, a moon, hot air balloon, extra stretchable planet, or literally on the sun, are you a bit warmed up by chance?
Then you're most likely reading this in a country. Okay, so this is kind of basic. Let's see. So Russia was named after the Rus people of Rus, you know, the Rus were a tribe of Vikings who were thought to have come from Sweden in the 9th century.
I'm gonna comment with Russia. Okay. It's not that the name comes from the old Norse term roads meaning
The men who row as rowing with the main way that rods and all the Vikings traverse the waters around them
Well, you know, I think I think I think of Andrew. I think of the roux plant. I think of the druids. I don't know
Maybe that's just me
Australia is the country of the aboriginals of people who have their own amazing mythology
Okay
Yet the name what we know the country by today has its roots in Greek mythology the group
He's had a god for everything Dionysus with the Greek god of wine
Pripyas with the god of the vegetable garden, but the Greek god
We are interested today is noctis or no no toast the Greek god of the southern wind
the Romans adopted
Greek mythology for themselves, but one thing they did change was the names of the gods.
Zeus became Jupiter, Aries became Mars, Notius' name was changed to Oster by the Romans.
With the name of the god in the southern wind being Oster, the name became in turn for
south and southern in Latin, and Latin is a language with a huge influence on the English
language.
Well, isn't that interesting? Okay, isn't that fascinating? Okay
So it goes through a lot of these names, you know the Isle of Man, which I'm what is Japan named after?
You know Japan has I think it's named as Nippon or something like that
The Japan's famous nickname is land of the rising Sun
That this nickname also shines some light see what I did there on the country's actual name too
The name is this roots all the way to Chinese Jin Poon which translates to the sunrise Jin Poon Japan
The Chinese refer to Japan by this name due to where the Japan is in relation to China
Japan is east of China and of course it's from the east that the Sun rises
The names of Japan are often associated with China as ancient China had a huge influence on the early civilizations in Japan
Okay
That interesting I don't know I'm just
You know, we want to have a request for a note. I can tell you about Chicago, Liverpool, Sydney, Budapest
and a lot of other places. I can tell you about the Eiffel Tower, I can tell you Statue of Liberty.
Yeah, there's just a lot of information out there. Some of it's interesting. Taj Mahal, kind of interesting. There's a lot of fascinating
stories, you know, the gorilla, where that came from.
Gorilla was thought to be a tribe of hairy women or even just long-haired black women
That's from Hannibal, right? I don't I mean that's just kind of it's kind of
offensive offensive to
Everybody okay, let me see
giraffe
There's actually something called the bandicoot the bandicoot
Pigeon bald eagle the puffin who's not a puffin puffins for sale this happens. Okay, bullshit canaries my grandma used to look canaries
First paradise you have to look up with those some time. Okay. I'm just sharing some of your suit trivia. How's it?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I
Don't not forget people kind of zone out when I read some time. I thought I had an interesting voice
Yes, not okay, let me see
Happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens, happens,
Happens for Sam
happens
Happens, it's a bit sharp. It's a sharp little Mary Poppins. You got it. You got the prize. You got it Mary Poppins good for you
Yep, you can also there's a movie called mr. Banks guys you can check out
It's a Disney movie. It's like, you know, it's like one of those like live-action ones. It's all about how
They made that movie and like how hard it was to get made because the author was just a pain in the butt to Disney, right?
She didn't like the animation. He didn't like
It was not he didn't take it the story seriously. Oh, this works. Okay, this works good right here. So
She didn't like it, but can you imagine you know how classic Mary Poppins is and the whole the freaking author of the whole book
Do you like the movie? I mean that is not an endorsement, but it was a fabulous movie. I think
Disney's gonna be very, very mass, you know, it's all about the
Survey of the many people as you can with the
You see illusions basically entertainment. Okay. Well, I mean
Pretty good tools are pretty good grim Reaper Network, what's that?
Is that work? Is that work? Hold on, hold on. Ziggy. Uh-oh. Joe's there in the chat. He's gonna start trouble. Joe, you're starting trouble.
I'm gonna post the link. Let's do it. What is the Grim Reaper Network? Is that, is that, is that the IP2?
That's what you got everyone nominated me for. I'm on the way out, probably. What the hell? Come on.
Grim Reaper. I just call him Grim. I call him Grim.
He has a little frown on his face.
It acts like it's the end of the world, but she means never is for him. It's usually it's for everyone else, but
I guess not easy seeing everybody go
Okay. Oh, here I am. Hey, look I yeah, okay myself there lights are on
Hi guys to watch. Oh, well to watch how many lights do I have I was funny when watching I have six lights
And now I have seven, okay
Push the link. Oh, well, but there is room. Oh, hi room. I know you're actual person. Everyone calls you grim. Okay
Again or grim, I don't know
Okay, everyone calls me psyche or psychic enough, so I understand because sometimes you will get the
IPTV is done. We're literally all site peak community out. Hey, you know what? I found somebody I really like
I mean, I've seen him before but I kind of like think he's cute now. His name is danger ranger
I don't know who you know that is
You're from across the pond. Hello govna. Hello might you might you?
Blimey day. I'm sorry. I don't know the language that will you can't download this but it's okay
I think the Discord link, guys, if you are able to join it and you want to,
I do have a Discord. You can just contact me there and stuff here.
There you go.
Yeah, well, we're just talking about Murray Poppins.
And so, you know, I do love, you know,
I have some friends who are Scousers
and I have my brother-in-law from Manchester,
pick up Benny and go to Danger's RV together, yellow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I like Danger, Danger Ranger.
I think he's really cute.
Oh, look who's here.
Guys, I just heard some sirens, who could it be?
It's the son of the police.
Whoop, whoop, it's the son of me and Psyche.
And then, and then, whoop, whoop.
Yeah, but I'm a great leader, so Psyche around
is between me fucking you in the ass.
I'm going to guide you to the Zessel.
Okay, well, I should I should start their channel. Let me see. I gotta subscribe to their channel. Are they a stream?
Grim Reaper's an old man from the UK, unfortunately.
Come up Grim.
Wow!
Cool, it looks like, or have a nice channel and like a very smart, you know, you have 80 nice subscribers.
I'm just... No, good or short. Good or short. One of us top shorts is me.
It is I have to go see it. I just I just saw it. Yeah, I said the queen's the side or mama bear or some notion
I'm looking her. Oh, we have to remove hello
Hello, how are you?
Oh my God, I can't believe you came up, you motherfucker.
What do you expect me to do with Alex after such a wonderful request?
Oh, bro, I love you. Jesus.
You know how much you guys have hurt me, bro?
I'm still trying to heal from that shake, Grim.
With you and Mabel.
Nothing to do with me?
Yeah, I did, because you were up there.
Like, I'm a friend, I'm Grim.
And then I heard you I heard you in the background. Oh, what is that?
He says what network is this? I see a hyper
history we have
Hyperborean, what does it say with what network here? What network is this here?
We can't really see it. It says the
Hey, okay, hold on. I don't know. What did they say network? It's something in a network. Yes
Okay, okay
I get it. It's a little small. It's a little small. It's a little hard to see. But yeah, I see it now. Okay.
You got to check out the mellows. What is it?
It's like, it's like, if I can get a word in, it'd be great, but I come in peace.
I don't come in here to come here to start any wars or bring any crap to you whatsoever.
Easy recommended me to come across.
I came across when his channel closed down a couple of days ago, I've listened in.
I like what you do.
I don't mind banter, banter is okay, don't have a problem with that.
I don't attack anybody, contrary to what Alex may or may not think.
I never said you attacked anyone.
Don't make me worry.
All I want to know, bro, is how is BBA in Melos?
Oh, that's all life. That's all life.
That's all life. Thank God.
The reason? Just? Absolutely not.
That's all I care about.
BBA, Mel's and Grimm, the double seven-band boys, I was wanted.
Remember that?
Listen, let's agree to disagree.
This is the Tower Show, this is a psych show.
I don't want to bring any personal grief into it.
It's nothing to do with anybody.
You know, I came up here because you asked
and that's the reason why, you know, I don't hide from anybody.
Thank you for coming up. I appreciate it. I love them people come on the panel. It's amazing and now psych
You just open a doorway to a whole different world because Grim Reaper is
In London right there on the across the ocean from us and this is a whole new world and his friends are
Like our youtubers in England with a hundred case subscribers
bare brain audit
Eyes on the audit these people like on geniuses. They they can all I don't know how to describe it, but you just
Opened the doorway into the next chapter. So grim
You know
I come in peace. I don't come here to cause any disruption. What? Yeah, they're so cool and they can help you when you help them like
the greenery
Computer shit like um
Green Reaper and mellows. They're like a graphic designers. I don't know what they are
But they used to be on TVP and will make cartoons for them
Like you know how the DJ lecture like you would mean the in the bushes
They will make better ones better than the one of you would say man like the fucking remember that bullshit better than that
Yeah, um as I was saying, um
The network is a network of people across the globe all with one aim, and that is to ensure
I was my mum a bit. I was my mum a bit.
We don't have a Bill of Rights. We don't have a Constitution as such. What we have in the UK
is permissions which have been given to us. You have rights. We have permissions. Cops have
duties. Simple as that. I stand up for the Bill of Rights because I believe that it's the Bill of
And people will argue and people will turn and say you shouldn't agree with First Amendment
or the terms etc.
I don't agree with everything that, I'll rephrase that, I don't agree with the way
that it's all done because there's some good ones and there's some that just go out for
clips and views in my opinion.
You know, whereas I believed it, you know, everyone should stand up for what they believe in and what they're right
So I've been here a long time. No, see big year here
Yeah, I'm here. Yeah. Okay. There you hi
Hello, yeah, no, I agree. I agree with what he's saying. Well, yeah, I mean I do too and it's like so nice to have you know
It's like it's even like, you know, even
You know, he's a citizen of the UK, and still he appreciates these rights, and you know...
Yeah, there's some...
I mean, because, you know, it's, in my opinion, it's a morality thing.
But if they don't have it, you know, everywhere, they don't have the Bill of Rights.
They have it here.
They don't have it very many other places, you know, I think there's...
Right, and I was like a lot of the work is for what to do. So what are you trying to say is that the Bill of Rights goes out the window and now it's a new
Grimm I'm talking about
And just treat everybody like they are you because they are
Everybody's going through a difficult life. You don't know what the person next to you is going through.
What does that mean? A difficult life?
Just treat everybody like they are you.
You understand? When you meet anyone on earth to encounter somebody, just pretend they're you
and treat them like you want to be treated.
The golden rule.
Because they are you.
Right. Yeah, I mean that was like, like he said, the golden rule.
Yeah, like that's what I did, but like what's your problem?
Can I just correct the miscommunication here?
The Bill of Rights in America, every American and every legal visitor to your country is
Legal, by the way, he's...
Yep, I'll say legal, right, or all protected by the Bill of Rights and they have those
rights anywhere in the U.S. When I went over to the U.S. and visited the U.S. 18 months
or so ago, I had all the Bill of Rights except for two. One, I couldn't vote and two, I couldn't
I was protected by the Bill of Rights. Now there's no other country anywhere that gives you that
protection and that's the reason or one of the reasons why I believe that the Bill of Rights
should never be interfered with by any government, state or even town council with all the ordinances.
Anything. No, no one. It's not even not even state nothing federal. I mean
Supreme Court rules, right?
Well, that that right at the Bill of Rights, and if it's you know, there are some decisions that they make that I think is a little bit wrong
However, you seem you seem knowledgeable about the US. Are you?
Yes
I am because I think it was just to warn you.
He's like a fucking fish and says from hell.
He knows everything.
This is a very knowledgeable man.
So don't go down that route.
Oh, no, I am.
I want to get on the ropes.
That's no, no, go ahead.
Go ahead.
What happens?
Perfect.
Oh, no, no. Do you not think it's funny? I'm going to actually sum it up so it's not a long story.
But do you not think it's funny with the Confederacy being Democrats? And now it's opposite.
Well, that's because that's because the meaning of the parties have really changed. You know, they're right. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
I mean, but that's that sometimes parties evolve and but they're actually just
Exactly the same thing
Well, I thought that was I thought that was weird, you know, you have pink hair people and the Confederates would have been like
Probably rolling in their graves
Same thing. They're under a pose running pink with all the red red and white and the flags and stuff like that
Yeah, what is it that rainbow thing? Yeah. No, no, no, no. No, no, no. I don't agree that anyone should be allowed to get away with defacing
I was just gonna jump in. Now you guys are done. Like, okay. Okay. Guys, am I gonna get, am I, am I, am I, am I in trouble now for wearing that speedo?
Guys, it was, it was. Yes, yes you are.
You disgraced the American flag.
I did not, I did not, I did not.
Yes, you did.
What would Trump think about that?
Think about that, homeboy.
And we said that we need to Trump.
You'll be in fucking what time we'll be right now, bro.
Alex, Alex, Alex.
It's not, it's not, calm down, okay?
I don't want you to, you're just giving the stuff out right now.
At least get boxers, you know, if that's what you need.
No, but it's true, don't lie to me, bro, it's true.
If Trump sees that, you'll be in fucking Alcatraz.
Alec has not an active prison, and I'm not even sure about what's on my fever. Hey guys, let's not talk about these things, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very, they're very
Alex, why are you first of all you're screaming at me? I mean, it's like so loud. It's like, wow
Then you're yelling stuff I say let's not talk about music you're taking teeth
I don't want to talk about okay, so Alex slow your roll, mister
Okay, can can you play glycerine by no, I can't play guys guys you can you can always you know, and you know
You can play songs or
I can't play songs on my channel.
Why can everybody else play songs that you can't?
Because I'm monetized as long as they're copyrights. They can lead to strikes. They can lead to like lose your money
Listen, it's my favorite song. That's a good song. Play it. Okay. No, no
Yo, come on, you gotta play psych fuck that you get
Sorry
Yeah
No, it was a nice Tuesday night. He's demanding. I've been playing a song that I told him
He's sitting in a green room for a few minutes. I know them. It's like, you know, you know
I do I know it
This is
I was in 90s. I was in 90s. No, and you guys can't even do it right you get
The let the days go by
Da da da da da da da da da da da da
I know the theme, but I just can't remember the words exactly
Yeah, but you guys are like doing it too high whenever you guys sing or something
I don't know
The let the days go
No, that's not how it is
Do let the days go by
No, you sing it
I'm never alone
I'm alone all the time
Oh, that's a sad lyric, yeah
No, you're doing it that way. You do it like you're
Okay, you're my music coach. Okay. Okay. I mean it's like I'm not I'm not gonna prove it
Yeah, stop me singing to him that please
You're you're the one talking
I'm not no they said that I didn't say that was not a grim reaper did not ask me to I'm never alone
I'm alone all the time. Hey stop. Here's you're making me stop. Stop singing that song
They're making me so you're sad. Yeah, you're making me sad
My fingers are numb. So it's slowing typing down. Oh, I'm sorry. Me as though tight. Yeah
Yeah
come on
Michael bro your boat is sure. Hallelujah. I'm singing that one. How long that comes to my
Okay, wing below
I mean, at this point we might as well hear Chubby Checker.
I don't know Chubby, I don't know Chubby Checker, I don't know any of his songs.
Do that twist!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, do the twist!
It's a twist, is it a twist?
Yeah, yeah!
It's like Dingaling.
It's like Dingaling, it's a twist, it's a twist.
Does he also sing like...
You must have played with your own Dingaling.
That's all I'll say.
Oh my god, well...
I can't sing that one, so.
I'm so knee-allegedly.
Very allegedly.
Here we have Amanda.
Hi honey, how are you?
Oh my God, that's female, thank God.
Pause the traffic.
Hello, I'm just...
Hey babe.
But I just heard somebody in the town just like Gotti on a beat his channel and he was you know
Gotti was just on my fucking telephone and he was acting like he wasn't on my door
It's weird. It's like oh my gosh Gotti. Why are you got his play pranks again? God is known
the uh prolific Frank's playing pranks again yeah my gosh he's a boy though i love it i'm like
okay all right i know that i can tell it's him and beat him to know it's him i can tell it's him
and he was like he's okay we're just gonna do it no no no you don't get it you don't get it no he
actually called my phone okay and he was acting like he was like through at and t well i don't have
How long did he pull you for?
Is it usually?
No, I'm quite a minute.
Yeah, no.
Okay, okay.
Okay, I don't know, I can be sort of slow.
Yeah, one time he left my panel and he had to scream
and I was seriously concerned that he had fallen
out the window, but I think he was just,
he played the sound effect or something.
The other days go by.
Okay, how do we do it in chat tonight? We're having a great night. Yeah, we have a manda and
The grim reaper here. Hey, wonderful. Wonderful guys, you know, I don't know happened as big. I think he dropped off. I think his
his uh, his voice
Knocked him off the show. I'm not sure. Yeah, hopefully
Today
Me and bird had to go back to the vet today. Oh
How's kitty cat? Well
birds my
Yes, I'm sorry. It's okay, honey. I do have a cat his name is her name is Thumper
Here, I'll show you a picture of Thumper. Let me find it
How do I change this I see
Baby, I don't like Vinnie talking shit
when he said i'm bad energy imagine that
man how is everyone saying that they were
saying that on beatus yeah there's no why
would they say that why would they judge
i'm bad let me think um come on grimm
why would they say that grimmie do you
imagine you remember you said the
you remember you said the furry diamond
that's that's that's that's the more
bad thing i don't care
I'm trying to understand why I was put backstage, I don't get it.
Brim, brim.
You're saying I'm bad at it.
Because when people annoy me, I can just kick your ass backstage for a minute if I want to.
So I was mulling.
I mulled the backstage.
I told you, I didn't know anything.
The song is making me too sad, and you're just seeing them in every conversation.
Yo, hold on, hold on, Grim, you still have the red scooter, is that it?
Why did I get put backstage though, I don't understand that.
Stop whining about being put backstage, because you know what, if you're asking why would
I put backstage, you're obviously not backstage.
That means you're back on stage, and so stop living in the past.
By the way, there is an account called Princess Lane in the chat.
I don't get it.
Well, you don't hear that. It's okay. Life isn't there, okay?
You don't have to understand everything.
You're the mastermind.
UJT and God.
Why?
Why Ziggy?
on your own show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can run your show, you can
Yes, you are. You're on the show. I don't want to hear you.
But what about how you're not on the show?
Yeah, I keep coming.
Who the hell is that crazy spunky girl?
Why do you keep hitting me, though?
That's what I'm saying.
She's so funny with a chubby cheese.
I hit that can. I hit that can.
And that's why I did it, because I have mobility.
That was it because you can because you have power.
Okay.
Yeah, by the way, I have a theory.
Burdo, burdo, think burdo is a bloody diamond.
Oh
When we see her or him it's peak hours. There's all peak
That's
Man and burdo is a transgender. I believe but I don't think yeah, it's actually that's number one thing
Number two thing they told the sakura saying bird or something. Oh my god
Yeah, that's funny. I mean, I think Birdo I swear to God
Bird fly weird like whatever it's mixed or whatever here here man. Well, exactly. No purr flies that way only one bird
My sideways will have a wing hanging off and a fucking dick hanging out, you know what I'm saying?
You can't duplicate that bird, you know, my boy gets it.
Haha, that's only one bird, boy.
That's flono.
Oh, it's flono.
I don't know about that, I don't understand what he's saying there.
No, it was scary more than Florida flying away with a cock and half a wing is that nobody
gets it, but him.
That's more scary.
Well, no, yeah, well, yeah, it was fucking...
Let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let
Bro, we're gonna have to learn more school to stay on these panels because anything you say
Psychic takes you so we're gonna have to come over some secret language or something
Talk on your own show Alice don't come on my show screaming
He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay guys. He's okay
I think it's kind of, you know...
Yeah, sometimes you can't have a conversation without problems, you know, just the way things
are. I mean, I'd rather say you can't a minute to speak. Yeah, yeah, I appreciate it. But
you talk, you were trying to explain earlier something that you didn't want to talk about
politics, and you know, he's talking about controversial stuff. I already mentioned tabs.
Why do you get mad about it?
I'm not mad, I'm totally calm right now, but if, or let me from G'day Mad, I have to like just remove my presence, just bear with me while I run my own show.
You know
So all time, you know, it's like like the
I just wish that you would play I wish that honestly that you would play that
Okay, if you say if you say it one more time, I'm gonna I'm gonna ask you to go for the night
And now you're really annoying. I've already said no several times and explain why not keep bringing it up
Okay, you don't want to play I'm gonna swing my cigar and I'll be a fine
And I see that a smoker cigar and it's in the chat or if you want to listen that song
You know, I think it's for free nice. Can you be nice to me and everybody day team everybody?
No, I can't like I have to be very
That is so weird why always JT
Here's the leader, right or the stupid cult? I don't I mean they always suck his dick give JT
Oh, right JT what he just said. I just almost cringed like I just want to scroll down my skin
Why would you why would JT have some like brain power? We
I will kick this asshole right now, and JP to all of them, and tell them who owns the show.
You know being that being that you know, you should please Alex. No, you don't
I said Alex I didn't think yeah, Ziggy you're you're a whole other thing where it's like, you know
You just have to learn to be happy, you know being part of the chat. You know, it's like
Oh, yeah, I'm I'm very happy to be a part of the chat and I know you sound you sound you sound you sound miserable
You sound great. You're very sad. And I'm sorry. I can't make you smile. You know, I'd love to like, you know
Oh, no, no, you make you make me smile and that's what I'm saying. Oh
That that, you know jt is uh, really
Wow JT
Well, is this the same city from earlier and all day long because they sound like some depressed ass
Oh, like JT like what is going on right now, bro
Who is the city?
The real city because this is not the city I've heard for the past three days
This is a completely different person unless you're crashing
Accusing everybody like three diamond is burdo and JT is you know
It's too confusing it gets too confusing and then it's like that they make sense anymore and then I'm in Alice in Wonderland all over
I just got out of that rabbit hole.
That's my favorite moment.
My favorite part is the little door.
She falls through the thing, the rabbit hole,
and then she eats the treat, and she gets real big.
Then she has to drink to get small.
And then she runs and finds the imaginary cat and then she starts crying and then her tears turn to the other because she's so big.
Wait, isn't JT the one that came around and he was like, hey, I found you.
Let's see who this other guy, guy, guy, guy, guys, let's go back to one to the other, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys, let's go back to one to the other guys
Enjoying the join the show at least it's been a content and I'm not there's a bad person
Now you're in court and you fuck
He didn't gonna spend like 10 decades in jail by the way. He's fucked. It's the same thing here
You think we're not watching and listening and now you're here. Now you're in court, brother
Can I just say something? I just read something quite funny in the chart. JT was referring
to this being Alice in Wonderland. I was just wondering how many rabbit holes do you go
I thought it was for me
Yeah, look at me a lot of them because it's like, you know
Can you do me a favor?
No, okay. Here's your favor. I'm gonna stop asking you for favors. Okay. Stop asking for favors. Okay. I'm gonna sit here with
Groom right now. Okay
Ziggy and Alex you guys are sufferable guys guys. It's not fun. It's not fun with you screaming at me
That he's whining. It's a good top back. Keep that cop. But they're both bad. It's just like there's both bad cops
You can't even reason with them
guys
You're ruining you're ruining the vibes for that. Okay, now it's
staying horrible names again.
Guys, stop it.
You have to sit back stage.
You can make out backstage.
I'm gonna talk to Grimmer now, man-to-man.
The adults are talking, okay?
You gotta sit at the kids table, okay?
I like the old one.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Yeah, so Amanda, are you happy, man?
I think I got...
Amanda, I think I have to try to fix things for everybody.
You know, I don't think people are being timed out.
I'm trying my best to...
Run run the panel and stuff like that, but guys stop it's not asking
Demanding stuff out of me. I don't know. I don't know guys. It's not pleasant. Okay
You could demand in the chat and then the mods will kind of dress
Mods might address you before I do if you're started demanding. I do something
You know, nobody really likes to be told what to do, right? So as long as I have freedom to do it
I want to do I'm gonna exercise that freedom
Yeah, what what is there anything you want to ask me sorry, I mean I want to ask you
Well, no, it's very very interesting. Yeah, it sounds like you know, so what we're about to the UK are you from?
I've actually moved to south Wales now. Okay. Okay. I was in Manchester, but I moved to south Wales
And I'm enjoying it. It's nice and quiet where I am. I live in the valleys, but it's nice and
The scenery is nice. I've even started to talk well
A little bit
The sheep the well sheep. Yeah
I am like, you know, I've done my ancestry, you know, we know we never know how accurate these those tests are but you know
And you have a large large wells large
UK a large
of Scottish and Irish and German, Swedish.
Let's face it, the majority of ancestors in the US can be linked back to Europe,
because of what happened many, many years ago, long before I was born,
or you or anybody else, but we're not answerable for what our ancestors did.
And I agree I agree with you, but you know, I guess that you know, there'd be a lot of the
People that disagree especially but there's there's even in California, which the state that never had had a like legalized slavery
Even California their seat their reparations are being sought for every single
I mean, it's like I think it's a little overkill which like, you know, it is hundreds of years later in a different
You know in a state that had never existed it, but
Well, they say that you should learn from your own history, I agree, but I also think
that people should recognise mistakes that have been made in the past, you know.
Vinnie, I can't help but whistle, mate, honest.
It's like you turning around and saying, I'm not talking to you because your great
ancestor was related to such and such, to such and such, and they did this.
Oh yeah, what the hell?
You don't do it at anybody, you know, even though I have the...
You know, I have friends with people that people don't like some friend of theirs and it's like it's like some huge some huge issue
And it's like and then they think because that their friend is has some kind of bad reputation
And it's like everyone has I've ever attached them as a bad reputation. I think we should just judge people on
You know on how they treat us and you know
feeling like how we want to be treated, everyone should be respectful and nice and kind of people
and then we can get along a lot better but people are always looking out for themselves and trying
to be selfish and everyone has to be number one. I get it. That's part of the problem,
unfortunately. I will say one thing, if I will respect everybody while they're respecting me,
Yeah, yeah, enough James Bond comment down. He sounds like James Bond
No, no, Ziggy so your mom's birthday is coming up. How did you know my mom's birthday my mom's birthday is today
Cuz you sound like you're 90, so I'll do this from page 200. I can't wait to get nice
Stop screaming out first of all and second of all is really don't ask him a people
Why are you screaming Alex Alex don't scream
My mother is 56 and she watches psyche
Oh, she does? That's very sweet. Hi, mom. Hi. How are you?
I call her. Yeah, she's a mumbet. She told me, huh? She told me.
All right, I won't yell. I won't yell. How old is the old one?
I don't know. You are your young one.
I'm 39. She had me. I'm 39. She had me whenever she was 16.
How old is the old bitch, bro? She said the question. 19.
Yeah, Alex, come on.
The fuck's your home? She said to number.
What is it? How old is she?
I didn't hear it. Say it again.
I already said.
Are you ready? So I didn't hear it.
What is this?
You're crazy, man.
Who is this guy?
You're insane.
The chance is on.
Hey, could you be shouting while you're recycling?
What is this?
I don't know.
When you figure it out, let me know, okay?
Come back later.
I don't need people telling me what is I mean, it's like please it's just the show
I don't know what it when you think it is the people talking on the show. It's the same
usually
Says yeah, thank you when you does the abracadabra. Yeah, I just followed your mom is she went crazy
Well, I mean, it's none of your business ally, but it's like I mean, but still I don't know
Why she's very condescending sort of. Oh, well
Whatever you said, it was boring. He's like, oh, well
He was saying it's a birthday, it's a birthday, it's a birthday.
Okay, Alex, Alex, please, I just want to say hi to BK, no one BK like him and a man
who has been with us for a very long time.
Thank you, what is this?
I just want to say hi to them.
I don't know
Daddy they're annoying me guys. They're annoying me
Dude, you know, hey, my mom knows gaudi too gaudi. She said she loved you
Yeah, well, he's very lovable. She's very lovable, but oh, he's
You guys she watches you guys
awesome
Wow, who's watching?
You don't know I'm watching
What your mom watches what?
Yeah
She's watching you good shit. Oh song right my mom watches what yeah
You're special. You're special. You're one of those special humans. No
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we grew up in
I know you are a circus freak. You have small hands and it's not like cabbage, bro
Cabbage
Yeah
You're like little circus freaks with little dirty cabbage
She said what did your mom do and have a mom?
Yeah
Yeah, I think he
You sit back stage of the house for a while. Okay, calm down. You can talk to me. Okay. Oh my gosh. I mean, it's like
I can't I can't it's like it's like it's like two as they have a rope in my brain
And it's like and then I think a whining on one side and then a screaming on the other and it's like
It's like I feel like
Yeah, I'm wearing I'm wearing loud headphones out if he's on louder than I've ever been to my microphone
I mean, I mean no it goes up to 200 but it's up to 200
And he needs to scream at the top of his lungs.
And just, yeah, so he has his left, okay?
Oh, he said back there for another minute.
I just want to listen to, you know,
God, you left, I mean, it's like.
Everyone, everyone being upset goes, it's all calm down.
What you will find, certainly if you haven't seen it already, is
certain people will latch onto one thing and will then constantly wind somebody else up.
And that means that you can't have a conversation because they jump in.
And when you try to say something, you have to try and overshadow to be heard.
But, I mean, that's not good.
No, it's not good. It's a very bad way to communicate or getting a point across really and it's like nothing
It's solved. I really I do like to solve like you know solve things when it comes down to it
Do you do tarot readings by the way? Yes, I do if you'd be interested in one
I can do one for you right now. I am interested but I haven't got time at the moment
I've got to get ready for work because we're five hours at least in front of you. So
But I do tune in every now and again when you're live, and certainly when I'm working, if you're live, I'll listen in.
I might even get a chance to put a little comment in the chat every now and again.
I've listened to your shows and some of them are really interesting, some of them are like
shouting matches, but you can't necessarily always control that, you can only do what
you can do and put them in time out for a little while, but then when they come back
they just carry on, that's the way it is, but that's the issue for you, you know, at
the end of the day.
two people agreeing when there's stupid arguments going on or someone's calling somebody just
because they've got a voice which is louder than anybody else's, you know, it's just the
way it is.
I'm not going to mention any names because it's not there on YouTube.
Yeah, we all can imagine and everyone has experiences, you know, those kind of people
Spell it all out from the studio. Okay, here we go. Alex, are you here?
I'd never die on you, mate.
Oh, Grim, you were 90.
No.
When I made you three years ago, by now you're going to be 95.
Yeah, we all like it.
You don't have to say anything hard.
It was a voice box.
It was a voice box, by the way.
Thank you.
Grim has a voice box.
Okay, who in here?
You heard it.
He sounds like a little fucking decrepit old man.
Why is he saying that?
So we bought a voice box and now it's like I'm great.
Okay, I I simply said that my mother was listening to you. I know I know
A little bit
My mom my mom listens to you. I know yeah
I mean, I don't know how to bring up. He's and you put me in backstage and my mom was like was what the fuck
She texted me. What the fuck?
Yeah, sorry mama. Sorry mama, you know, it's like, you know, I know you maybe you had to put on timeout too, you know
So, you know, he's like a little bit
You know what she actually said she was like I had to put him in the bed at certain points tail
Yes, but yeah, it's a free so we know it's a free uh
Your your free spirit can't it's hard to control anybody but it's hard to tell you what to do
It's hard to tell me what to do. It's like we're not gonna get anywhere just telling you what to do
It's always
That's a person though that is like trying to take over you though. No nobody's gonna take over me, okay?
There's no vacancy there's no vacancy
Before me he was saying
I don't know his name. I don't know his name. Hey guys. Hey, hey, Brian
We're gonna say allies you either have to just accept him or let him up or not either because you won't change
Yeah, oh, I know. I mean it's like that's him and there's like, you know, sometimes when you're dealing with the person with like, you know
Alice is a little bit
I mean, I'm nobody because what is sanity really bells, you know, you get a little bit
I know I get a little bit crazy too, right? Okay. So, but yeah, it's like and you can't really reason with them. He's
He's done some things that make sense to me, but I was talking about the British guy, he's right here, he's in the chair right now.
He was down the earth, yeah.
Well he's down the earth, he's an even being, we all are down the earth.
In my defence, I apologise to any snowflakes out there, I do say how it is, I don't dress it up.
Just recently I found out that my wife is very ill at the moment when she's going through tests at the moment
and she's had a biopsy done when trying to find out whether or not she's actually got cancer or not at the moment.
But when I told my son, and yes I do have a son, unrelated to me, just for those idiots out there,
was very blunt and I just gave the facts and I didn't realize that I was so
blunt yeah that is what life is you know you look at
whoa these guys life is yeah
I can't control what's going on externally and what the hospital is doing, etc.
So, I'm not worrying about it.
Alex's problem is he doesn't know what's going on internally with him, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, we've all got shit going on behind the scenes, haven't we?
Yeah, yeah. Alex has done a lot of cocaine, you know, it makes it all movie, okay?
But it's actually something called a serenity prayer, a serenity prayer.
Uh, and this is like, you know, it's something to say in these moments where we're like, you know, what do we have control of?
It says, God, uh, uh, grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change.
Oh, I thought, like, okay, no, go.
I mean, no, it's like a whole prayer.
It's like a whole little poem.
It's like, it's what, you know,
it's interrupted with the non-related question.
It kind of takes away from it.
So I just wanted to read it completely, okay?
What is that?
So, the prayer to accept the things that we cannot change.
Cause there's some things we don't have control of.
We don't have control of a person's mind.
We don't have control of the sun coming out tomorrow.
You know, a lot of these things are just taking care
of by nature or other people, right?
So there so we have to accept sometimes we there's things we cannot change and it's like, you know
You know, we can try to paint the red the white roses red and bright and we're spoising the roses, right?
This is a cream
Yes, I'll let me
You wife is sick. What's wrong with the old Alex? Alex, what are you doing?
Okay, he explained it out of reason why you're being insensitive and you know, not not a
No, he's not it's carbine insensitive. He's been
Wild yeah, he's being off the wall. Yeah, listen Alex doesn't worry you make at all
And like I said you look at what you can so yeah, yeah, it's like Alex is Alex
He's always has been yeah
He's that he's that way sometimes and he's not that way, so I mean he can
All credit to Alex when he's not
Drinking or anything like that. He's a really good guy. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, but there are times
When that's overridden by his other side his drinking. Yeah, I know I've seen yeah
I'm not playing any any cartoons Katrina not today
Hey, I haven't got time and be it's not my show. Yeah, I don't think I don't think you I don't I don't be
Yeah, so let's uh
The only thing I have to say to Alex is that that was kind of messed up because you got me for backstage my mom was
talking. Okay. Oh, my God, please. Hey, no, I can't hear about your mom. I'm praying for your mom,
but don't talk about it. Don't talk about it. Don't talk about it. Don't talk about it. Don't
my mom watches him that was it i don't know but it's a kind of almost like in
fur like your mom i don't know what you're saying you're trying for you
he said he said my mom had cancer that was a weird
i don't like it i just know that i mean i mean it's like you know it's funny that it's like they're
So, you know, it's insane, but I say, hey, don't say that he's screaming things that you're not supposed to say, right?
It's like, you know, it's not funny anymore, Alex. I don't feel like he should be on the rest of the night.
I think he should be the rest of the night off. I'll donate the gong myself at this point.
Hold on. Alex, take the night off.
Ziggy, Ziggy, you're next, you know, Ziggy, you keep harping on me, just enjoy the conversation.
I don't want to hear anything about, you know, Bush, Glycerine, or, you know, you got put
backstage, okay, like, you're gonna get put backstage again, and so now, now we're gonna
have this one.
I don't want to hear about it, I got three backstage 20 minutes ago, okay?
That's, that's old.
I was, I was the one that was talking about my mom, like, loves you.
What's going on with you guys?
I'm okay.
I don't know the situation with the people inside.
My mom is messaging me right now and she's like,
what is going on?
I don't believe you, I don't even believe you.
I don't even believe you.
My mom listens to you every day.
I wouldn't have her call on the show,
I wouldn't have any talk to her myself.
I haven't been up there for forty-one.
I'm not yet.
Well, yes.
Oh.
They're and I know it better not be a woman a woman's voice and a voice changer
This is like you. Okay. I was just banned from be this for good for doc. Oh my gosh. Yeah, he did that. That's not cool
Alex. No, he's he never be loud. He can't
Is that gaudy?
Yeah, Gaudi, Gaudi, what are you doing, buddy?
What's going on?
Hey!
Man, my mom tried to-
Can you hear me?
I can't hear you.
I've lost my hearing.
I can kind of hear him, but can you turn him up a little bit?
He has control of his microphone, so Gaudi can turn up his microphone if he would like to.
Yeah, your mic's a little...
I think your mic is high, let me look at your mic once again.
Oh, yeah, turn me down then.
It's not even all the way up, but why are you so loud?
It's so loud once again.
Very close to the mic.
Yeah, it's just too close to the microphone.
You put it a little bit away from your mouth like that,
and then it's like you'll still pick up the words
that won't quite be, you know, breaking my ears.
I actually was, you know, injured by being...
S-T-A-B-B-E-D in the ear with a sharp object before, so I just said that again.
What did you just spell out? What was that?
S-T-A-B-B-E-D.
S-T-A-P-E-D.
B-B-E-D.
Steps?
Mm-hmm.
We can't say that? We can't say that?
Well, I know, I know, I know, I know, it's just a violent, I just don't like violent language, but, you know, it's like we can say.
S C A B B easy. I don't know. You can say whatever you want. We just got to spell it out. Yeah, spell it out
You can a code word spell it out, you know, anywhere you want. Yes
Any word you can just you can say there's a code word for everything. Okay, just learn it
use it
And we'll all get the idea. We don't need people are just like so. So there's anything on panel
That's it's like I'm not gonna fall for it. You said okay. I'm not gonna fall for this trap. Oh, no
Why do you think that I am not a grim reaper but a grim paper?
Just out of curiosity.
Play on words.
It's obvious you're Alfred Hitchcock.
I'm out for what, sorry?
You're Alfred Hitchcock.
It's well
You don't know me. I don't know you let's just leave it at that. Shall we I truly enjoy
You're very very you're very very cryptic, you know, I've seen psycho I've seen
Northwest I've seen rear window. I've seen many of your films
Something I think there's something in quantum physics. It's called the observer
Have you heard of this effect of the observer effect?
Let me see.
There's somebody observing.
What does that do?
So the observer effect refers to the phenomena where an act of observing a system inevitably
alters that system.
The effect is prominent in both quantum mechanics and behavioral studies impacting how phenomena
are measured or understood.
Essentially the very act of observing, especially with measuring instruments, can change the
of what is being observed.
That's interesting to think about.
Hold on.
So in a minute.
You like to watch.
Is that so, Psyche?
You like to watch?
No, I really don't.
I mean, it's like, I'm more of an exhibitionist.
I like to, I like to get this video.
I like to get this video.
I don't like, I don't watch for people,
but I'm not like a watch.
I'm not like a collector of information.
I'm not like a spy.
I think I'm more of a.
I'm very poor at freedom.
I'm very, I'm a little carried here.
You see the McCobb.
McCobb? Yeah, it was certainly, you know.
I, uh, I loved, uh, you know,
Marilyn Manson.
Good growing up.
Dark comedy.
Four movies, you know, the accent.
Yeah, yeah, he, he, he's, he has a little bit of a British accent.
I think we're...
You know, it's
Rubbing up on us Amanda. Yes, you think yeah, I know everything's going crazy in chat. See
Yeah
No, I do understand about you know people that getting uh, you know
Unfortunately, my father did pass away from cancer last year and I know that like a lot of people are you know
We're gonna be the baby boomer overcoming of age. You know that look we're losing a lot of them and
Did you say I don't know who you are
Who's I heard a woman's voice who's that woman's voice
Did you hear the woman's voice? I heard a woman's voice guys just there. That was his mother
That is that your real voice. That's your real voice. You're really a woman. You're using a voice changer guy
I hear the woman's voice. Your voice changer is glitching. Did everyone hear it? I heard a woman's voice.
Who is that? I heard my voice there too. What are you doing? Are you playing?
Hello
Are you playing games?
I'm not playing games.
I'm asking you a question.
I think you're playing games.
Good evening, Paige.
Good evening, sir.
What are you doing?
Life is a game, I think.
Playing games?
well okay well you can go go go back go with ziggie and you can go play chess or
hold on here you know I just wanted to party I want you to yell because the
Well
Alistair he kicked off. Oh, yeah, so yell at God
Stop you tell me you said you said like Madonna right now
God, do you know what she sounds like?
Dima Donna?
Good Donna, huh?
Dima Donna, the singer.
Okay, hold on.
Dima Donna is a singer, yeah, but um, yeah.
Oh, I can't hear you.
You're a little older than us.
Oh, God, you're a singer.
Oh, my God.
Oh, she doesn't quite sound.
Well, she sounds a little...
She's scared.
She has a female voice.
Oh gosh good guys with that West Side story. We don't have to we don't have to be you know rival gang
Who are these people? I only know cage. I only know psyche. I know that like Ziggy guy with the t-shirt
No, I don't know. I think there are some kind of like discords, secret society, I don't know if it's on the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off the off
It's all coming together now.
Where did Paige come back?
Paige, where did you go?
I didn't run.
These guys up there, they scared off Paige.
She doesn't want to be part of this ultrasonation.
There were too many cults.
God, we need to take one cult and just stick to it.
Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Colt Col
Okay, Gotti, you would know about snow because it's like, you know, you and Alex probably have as much cocaine as a scarface in your, you know, your desk drawer.
So leave me alone about it.
I thought Gotti was shit, but he ain't shit. He just literally got as God doesn't exist. I'm sorry for all the bullies.
Well, you let him know. You tell him.
I'm not that. I'm no longer a bulldog.
His name is Gott. His name is...
God, it's like, kind of like, I think it's like, I don't know, maybe this guy's the grand architect.
One and God is just one of us, just as large as like one of us.
Not like this fake Reaper dude.
I don't know guys guys. Can we all get let's all like I'm do voice lessons together and we can all like
Yes
I have a page in my book
I'm gonna see you later. I don't even be here. Okay
Later psyche. Bye. Later. Later. Later, bitch. Love you. Love you. I don't love you. I hope your
microphone dies on you tonight and you're like, oh, okay. Well, bye. We'll see you later. Um,
let's see. Um, let's see. So I do have a page in this book. I'm fat on this book. Let me see.
Where is this another? Oh, it's in my, it's in that book. It's in this one.
It's a page about why is it you so quiet?
Ziggy is not on the panel anymore. Oh, no, he is. Yes. But I do have this a
You know this thing with the vowels, right? It says
The tree of gallows or the ladder of vowels and it goes oh, I yeah, this is highway 61 US
Route 61 the blues highway, okay, and then it has like some kind of devil square like
Okay
Okay, and look so bad. I have this drawing. We've got it. See look at this drawing. See if this makes any sense
We go because I
Go oh, oh, I
Oh, IEA it's like to go
Oh, and then I don't know you's not in there, but it's just like the diaphragm
As it goes, I-A-E-O, you're gonna hail new oxygen, okay?
Okay, hello.
Hi, I ended my 60th panel,
like people to come here and I send them here
and you kicked me.
Everybody, I can do better tarot card readings than psyche.
Okay, okay, let's, here we go again, here we go again,
Vita, Vita, okay, Vita, okay, please, Vita.
You were being insulting to me and saying,
oh, you already, you were being insulting.
I just like to jump in.
And you're already leaving, and now you're going to make a big deal about it again, okay?
Beta. No, no, no, stop. Thank you very much for supporting the show.
Let me see. I don't know who this is. This is not Rado, though. I think this is a...
You kicked Page 2? What are you kicking?
I didn't kick him. Now, people are leaving like their signature. Okay, so Rondo. Okay, I want to beat this back there.
I just want to say one thing, and all kinds, everybody join me on BKG where I can reveal
psychicera cards. Okay, well, Bita, you know, it's like you're being a broken record and it's not
very kind. I don't ever mess with you and say, oh, you know, Bita, I don't even know what you do,
you know, you're wholesaling whatever. I don't know. I don't know. It's like, you know, why are you
You just stop it. You don't mess with around with my my my trade. You know, you know, you don't do it. Okay, don't do that
So, yeah, you know
Me
Yeah, that's what they say you're you were a washed-up actor back in the 80s. I'm washed-up actor back in the 80s
No, I was in I was in some like local community here
You know, it was in the street plays. I did drama in my school. Okay. Now. She's gonna you know, you're saying horrible things
I guess you're not gonna until you stop saying horrible. Oh point until you stop saying horrible things
I'm not really message me and he said it's gonna get another time
Okay, I believe I'm guys making stuff up. Hold on. Let me get home. I just maybe make sure these right people second
Can you get a face tattoo? Hello?
Hello, hello, don't say the n-word. Hello. Who's this? Why'd you say that?
Because I've been being an n-word bomb. So who is this? Who am I speaking to you? This is rondo
I've tried to come on before you always never you never let me on
Okay, rondo. So here's the question psyche. Um, you never let me. That's rondo. Yo, rondo. So
psych, I have a question for you. How long you've been doing this for?
Doing what? What's for YouTube stream? I've been doing YouTube stands like, uh, like, you know,
October of last year. I've been, you know, basically doing my life, my live streams
Is it good is it good for the psyche or no is it good for the psyche?
Okay, yeah
the book of uh, you know Persian poetry and I'll be also doing I'll start doing her also doing her version
chill chill chill dude I need you to chill
We would never do that to you
Calm down dude
No but she just did but she's insane
She's insane, don't let her on
Rondo, she's not insane that's fucking rude
also said she would never do that to you
That's what she just did she just said it several times
she's like oh I'm doing
She's never kicked you from her panel
Yeah, she's not bought me on before and I mean, I can't give you she was saying something very rude
You know like a little big deal thing. She's like, oh, I don't like you. She's like, oh, I don't like you
You can listen back to what she said to me. She's not too much. She takes her
Stop just give me a sec. I was totally
Everybody else all these random people all the time you're gonna take shit from them and let them come back and play
Let's play games, but like you can't say nothing
I brought back several times, but she keeps that she keeps like it was anything that aren't true and insulting me and trying to say
I love you, I love you, but that's not how it works.
Well, listen back, Paige,
because you didn't hear the whole thing.
And so, you know, you're not hearing the whole story, okay?
And so I know, you know, you're just gonna wanna like,
you know, just listen to what she's saying, okay?
Just listen back.
Just listen to what she's saying.
Just listen to what she's saying, okay?
Just listen back.
in an Oreo cookie and I can't be in the middle of every argument.
What is going on? What the hell is going on here?
I don't know. Everyone's feeling like there's a
chest be inside. Okay. People are pretending to be angry tonight?
I'm not pretending. I'm not really angry. I don't even get angry. I
just get like defensive. I get like, you know, protective of, you know,
Sometimes not everyone has someone looking out for them, right? So I get me sure to look up for myself
Hey, sir, I don't want to be rude. I don't want to be rude. Don't take us the wrong way. Um, are you are you autistic?
My god, I don't know. I don't think I've ever been diagnosed. He's very artistic. He's draws pictures. Yeah, music
No, let me see some more dude
It's like you draw his picture go ahead. I did well. I mean I don't have
I mean I don't have an idea
Choco, I mean he's I mean I can draw full screen. Oh fuck where you go
I can draw something that says, you know, the reaper network and stuff, but I just, I can't, I don't know what he looks like.
There's God here.
Come on, Roy, really?
That's a masterpiece.
It's like a fucking piece of shit.
It's like a fucking masterpiece.
You'll understand I didn't I didn't provoke her anything. I was being pleasant and then yeah
And then you know start attacking me for no reason and there's easy. I don't know easy cameras on this easy. Oh my god
He's holding balloons and the whole I think he's holding no he's holding a
So, no, he's holding on like a my favorite drinking with one dingle and ghost to my favorite single and ghost
Yeah, I did a couple I did dingle or it's there's dingle. It's one of Ingalls and then you know, I have uh, you know
I've sat these scarlet, you know, it's been her she's right there
It's a okay, and then uh time we all know we all know in the time from the chat
There we go. Yeah, everyone subscribe to beat his kiddies go over there, you know, it's like a you know, do you know her panel?
It's not a contest. I want to help everybody. You know, she's helped me a lot. I didn't say anything to conjure that. There's there's spunky
So we have
Okay, let me see money for 20. We've out here's allies of course allies in my pd. Yeah
Oh
That's all I'm a pd. He looks like a bike. He like got a little police bike
Um, he's a little a little twink car. There's sort of diamond guys three diamond
Can you draw? Can you draw rondo?
And try that's the best party diamonds ever gonna look just get a black marker like do a circle
And there's Christine
I don't think you know, you know, I don't think you don't want me to show her picture and I don't want to
Yeah, but I don't want to make rain matter that she already is but
Reason to be mad. Just just do it. Yeah. Yeah. I love you. I love you. Oh, wow
Okay, well anyway, that's why I beat his daddy probably beat. I'm sorry. I'm not bad. I'm not a good artist, okay?
Well, I think I'm okay. Let me see if you show your picture. You look like Jesus
Well, that's not very nice to say be that he's been talking this whole time. Has he been
Probably probably you know
Better a log or something. It's Los Angeles. So this is oh, yeah, hold on. What is my mod doing?
So what's the module? Oh, be oh, yeah beat is not crazy. The beat is my mod. Can you believe it? I mean, I
You think you think I you think I uh, I
Still love her what about who who who drew beat I thought I drew that
The pics are crazy well, you know, I'm a little crazy
Hey, I think he's the grim reaper. What do you think of that?
Who thinks of the grim reaper? This guy grim reaper. He thinks he's the real grim reaper.
Here's the grim reaper. I think the grim reaper is that...
It's a psychopalm, it's very associated with stater and father of time, cronos, you know,
it's like the planet Saturn, which is like my ruling planet, the planet of karma, the planet of
matter, the world coming to materialism, the planet of time actually, they know how to time,
and so yeah, that's interesting about it, but let's see what else, like Grim Reapered. So also
Okay, hold on one second, Ida, give me, go ahead, give me one condition, you say you
love me?
Yeah, I'll give you one condition.
Let me do a reading for you, Mr. Saiki.
I'll forgive you. You say you love me come back and you say that I'll let like one let beta do a one reading for you
That's not repetitive. You pussy-ass bitch putting me
Numbers one up, right?
Yeah, it's a missus. Do you want to hear reading or not from me? No, you're making it. I'll be you. Just make it
Shut up
Oh, not Alexander the McQueen. I do
No, nobody my ass. That's what you like. You like it bossy. Don't you you fucker?
No, I
asshole
I don't want it. I don't want it. No, I'm going to do your fucking reading and you're going to take it
Thank you. Hi Gotti, what's going on guys, baby? What's going on? Why are you people fighting?
Why is there a lot of fighting in here?
I mean, I know this is my little fucking life to come here and then he wants to be a bitch
And he doesn't want me to like do a reading for him
I'll do one for him. It will like open your eyes. I you will have the biggest fucking asshole awakening ever
carrot awakens
Now fuck you thank you for ever putting me backstage you can come back come back come back
You're gonna do the reading
I'll keep alec the alice backstage for the
That's what was missing. That's
It was the same
Yeah, yeah, I think I think I think okay, so I'll bring Alex back since it was over. Hey guys
Ah
Well, I'm out of here. You can have Alex. Yeah. Bye
She sounds like Minnie Mouse the don't bitch right we need like we need
Needs more
She's gonna fly off to Brazil again
She's gonna flap away
Okay, so Alice, okay, so Alice, what do you, wait, you're, now you're docking in summer, Alice, what's the deal? Like, what are you doing?
Her real name is Amber Duncan.
Hey!
No, Alex, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
He told you not to bring him on, I don't wish to be a platformer, I know, he's not worth the night, he just broke the rules for a serious place.
Everybody gets pissed in their fucking cornflakes this morning instead of milk.
Apparently.
That's disgusting.
Who would do that?
It's an upsetting thought, that's what this is.
It's all an act.
Everyone's going to be happy against it.
Yeah, I'm not serious, but like I don't like when my friends fight
Yeah, well, they'll be they'll be friends again tomorrow
They'll be friends in five minutes. Yeah, probably I was gonna say probably today
Well, I'm sorry guys, I'm sorry I'm gonna bump people out. I mean is like
I was just trying to hang out.
Everyone's mad at me. Everyone's mad at me for everything.
Everyone points your fingers at Psyche.
At least I can't be blamed for this.
God, it's all your fault.
Point your fingers at me.
Fuck you, it is.
The devil told me that you were conspiring against him for the whole story.
There is no devil, dumb dumb.
God you got me coffee. Don't call me dumb dumb. You're not
Only only who's like who's will goes can have that
I don't know it's like there's the world is duality right and so if there is a God you know
The God is in singularity if it's in the duality would come out
It's to talk about it's God and the psyche of the polarities will come out as the polarity
It's he really a part of giant joint that yeah
Wow, you know what it's like it's kind of but I said it's like you know the Willy Wonka test
It's gonna see who has a pure heart look who waddled in just wow
Okay. Wow. Wow, guys. Oh my gosh. The panel is just emptying out. Oh my gosh.
Uh-oh. Bye-bye. Okay. Oh my gosh. We just lost a little bit of weight on the panel.
What happened?
Guys, there's those ghosts in the machine. There's some kind of technical difficulties. Oh my gosh.
Yeah
This is rondo
Listen bro, get your permanent marker out. They're like you roll second one
I don't believe that's what you look like
I don't have I don't have enough ink ink for that. Come on, bro. Just draw a fucking circle. Oh
Just wonderful. He's just
Thank you. Thank you
Yes, okay, so Monica Monica wants it. I can draw a picture of Monica. Yeah, you're welcome
I know it's like, you know, you guys there's something called. There's a word. There's a word. I really don't I mean
It's like a word
The words not bad, but it's like it's like the way it's done. Okay, I'll tell you I'll put the word on a piece of paper
I don't want to say it's bad juju to say this word. I'll say this word
Okay, I'll say this is the word that I this is like one of the things that I really
Do you not care for
That's it gives you much away, but this
You read it smart smart. Yeah, yes, okay smart who's smart
Well, if you don't know that then
Maybe look up that's the thing you have to work that one out for yourself. Hello, Rhonda. How are you?
How you doing?
I'm alright, I just wondered if you know you were trying to say something about the grim reaper
you know I mean I take on the name, I look after a network of people, share some thoughts
and like mine did shall we say. So bit like on here there's a few people who are into
Psychology is best not to allow this to become a shit show, basically, excuse my language,
but a lot of panels end up that way with certain characters, you know, and I've been
sat patiently waiting to speak for about half an hour or so, because...
The panel was going in the direction. I didn't know anything
Comments, it's like the chat. I don't know even I don't even I don't know anything about where it goes
Yeah, I mean I said I have no idea what people are talking about. So it's like, you know, I'd rather
Not have it on my show or it's like I can't even respond to it because
Oh, by the way, if you're wondering how old I am, I was created around the back in the 1500s.
Oh my god.
During this time, it's been a fluid problem.
Apparently, I had to create it in the beginning of the first time that they received me taken away.
But that's a history lesson.
Yeah.
Like I was just playing doctors, counting, I would say like, yeah, but I really do think it's better, like, you know, with the hands, the sickle, and like, the death mask, you know, that was, especially during the plague, right?
I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did
More prevalence than I'm more people doing it. So it's accomplished my goal. So thank you so much
Part of my vision. Okay, what happened to page? Oh, I lose my viewers
I think that people with page page left because she's doing other stuff
I don't know everyone mad at me. I mean, I'm trying to do my best
Everybody mad at you Pat
because there's so many
Alexander because I can't talk you know, I can't you barely get a word in because there's so many people and they're saying like a
lot of strange things and some of the things are off topic and I'll say don't say this and they keep bringing it up
And if they don't do this
It was JT and you and Ziggy got it
I don't I don't know. I don't know. I must I'm I think I'm I think I'm losing my marbles guys
Again, there's no way no way
With the bike did you fix the bike? I have to they do you have like a repair you can get you know
Just the it's probably if you use the instrument place or something, so I'm gonna take it as soon as possible
How do you have some you know?
I have a little bit of a
ability
So, you know, save up a little bit now that I have the channel going so hopefully I'll be able to
Get it taken care of a
Yeah, I would grab a unicycle try to convert a little bit to
Do to a simple this case. Okay, so how about
You know motorcycle I really like a motorist. Can you give me a Harley?
Can I please have a Harley? I don't think you'd like a Harley. I could I could I could I could I could I could I mean I probably like
Probably fall off, but I can I can
What is that time you I'll just ride ride bitch you can drive it you can be like a bike
No, no, no, no, no, that's that's what that's your you know, we can wish the West
Yep
The dog. It was a dog. It was a dog. Oh, yeah. Yep. You have a cat. It was it was Toto and no
And I'm you know, Mrs. Goldsch did have cats and the Toto did chase the cats because Dorothy
Let's let the fucking dog run wild and do what everyone has to do
I mean, she that was her version of the glove
But it's actually you know, she should have like ran Toto in a little bit and say hey Toto, you know
Don't do that because I don't want to you know, you know, let's be separated and you know
You didn't came to the sheriff's office. We put down a total was a metaphor
Yeah, and the total actually total is the smartest one in the movie
He's actually the most innocent person in the movie. He was the one that the uncover who the wizard truly was
He was smarter than all the the all the other people combined so
Psych would you would you psych would you would you bang beat you guys seem like a good couple?
Well, that's the very interesting part, I'm gay, and so, you know, I'm like, bang women.
I'm kind of interested, you know, Chris K right now, some stuff he said, maybe, you
know, he wants to do some kind of threesome, whatever, whatever, whatever we'll do.
Let's do it, Chris.
Yeah, I don't think Vita liked me anyway, because she used to say I was, I was handsome
prince, now she says I'm like a, I'm like a evil frog, and so I don't know.
I'm probably in many many many lifetimes. Yeah
Yeah, old be the little be you know
He never changes. Oh be the same the same voice same if you look exactly the same. Okay, you guys act like very similar
We act very similar. Yes, we're both
With Queen or Queens in a way. She accused me of being a Colombian drug lord. Well
No, I mean Alex has actually admitted to being one and then then he got a job as the NYPD
I'm just I'm not sure what it's anyone so I told her that my name was else when you
I thought she accused you of being a serial killer. Okay. Okay. Let's thank you people big guys. It says no slander
So that means no accusing no slander. Oh, really for wanted to explain something to you. I think you said okay
Okay, I'm sorry remember go ahead. I'm sorry to cut you off. No, I wasn't saying is that I was just listening in
I'm thinking you're right about to so the book or the film did put that
Make totos the most intelligent character
on in the film
And then they you know, it was the latest version is sort of like ridiculous
And he was a key was a care and tear in the movie. He told it was a care and terrier. And so this is like a special
You know, I think from Scotland, right these this care and terriers and this you know, it's a very
Special kind of dog. I love a
I love those the spirit of these terrier. They are very very smart and we can learn a lot from dogs
You know and all animals actually okay, so how's the honor? How's the honor? You're gonna come search. Okay guys your earplugs
Hold on grim reaper. Did you say total is the most intelligent character in the Wizard of Oz?
Yes, yes, the dude from the clip
the little doggy
Yeah, yeah, it's more intelligent and Dorothy
Yes, the car really lot, you know all the whole thing everybody. Yeah, the dog. Yes. He's a smart boy
You know, how do you come to that conclusion asshole? And that's what you think sucks dick. You understand that's
Because you guys are retarded this guy you said a little dog is the most intelligent captain the Wizard of Oz
bro you're lucky and you might get convicted of that well you know he was a good dog
he was a good dog yeah good smart dog don't fuck off can i can i just say a never stop in the way
there are a lot
Yeah, you just do
So still never once fluffed its line lines and there was never a double take due to an error the dog made
Amazing
Total fucked up the whole thing the whole reason Dorothy got lost was cuz total ran into the bed
There was a wizard gave a ride home
Toto fucked up the brood right there, he's like one of those fine monkey kind of creatures, but I don't know
Um, you might be right with, oh with the Roller's case on
No, Toto, no, that's it, you're thinking of the wheelies, you're thinking of the wheelies, that's the return dog
Return to Oz, the return to Oz, the wheelies.
Return to Oz, that's nothing.
There are these, there are these, there's this bicycle or scooter game, kind of, you know,
harass, uh, harass Dorothy, you know, everybody else in Oz, so it says now...
Yeah. Yeah. Now they give it clear what's up and you guys are gay in those fights. Oh,
show me. Why are you saying a horrible thing? I mean, guys, stop acting. No, stop acting
like that. The panels are a bad example for you guys to follow. He may be gay, but he
can still kick your ass, shorty. Hello? Yeah. Okay. So anyway.
And I'm not not a violent person
You would play the clip from me the other day
of the
health of the
and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes
In the bushes, I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you
In the bushes
No, please, I didn't say anything
I don't want to
In the trees
No, please
I don't want to
Uh, I couldn't get ready to the real, uh, yeah, I don't know how I took off.
I don't know if I kicked him off this time.
So I was going to shock color.
Maybe we all look into that on Amazon.
I will get you.
Okay.
Shorty notes, red ink.
That's where I don't call everybody gay.
Okay.
You say, okay.
You say voice on effects me.
What does that mean?
So are you a girl?
Oh, and who is that?
I don't know.
Trans man.
I'm very confused.
Flirty diamond.
It looks like Flirty Diamond without looking at it.
Oh, shit.
It's diamond.
Sorry, God with Alice is confused now. I think burdo is 30 diamonds. I think
Shorty is a trans man
Okay, my birthday is actually one-seventh, so I'm going to reverse that.
Yeah, now for Erby.
And also, cancer is the opposite of capricorn.
And so, I'm at least six months from my birthday pretty much.
Almost about six months.
Erby, hey Erby, how are you?
Erby.
Yeah guys, it's getting a little hectic.
I'm trying to, you know...
Have a fun show. I'm trying to have a fun show. I'm just trying to chill. I'm just trying to chill.
I can't. I got guys. I got people putting black magic curses on me.
You know, I have monsters. I have military people in the chat. I have people are...
having multiple personalities disorder people are flandering dogs I mean it's
like guys you know drama than yes you know all of the television combined okay
so I mean you guys I mean it's all here I mean nothing now it's all go to the
gym
You're cool. It's my day off. You're drunk. So, it's okay. It's okay. It's fine.
You're still drunk. That's not the thing to do. Now, play a piece of the drama, I guess.
Play a piece. You know, Paige, you're so nice.
Like, people just walk on over the show. I love you, Paige.
So, I can't hear you. Okay. Good night. Bye.
Have a good night. Have a good night.
I'm gonna sort of work out.
Dennis, it's always good to see you. Nice to meet you.
I can't hear you at all. Thank you.
Hold on. Why did, why does Page come over here and grow balls?
Oh, sorry. I'm out there. See you later, guys.
Page comes over here and grows balls.
No, I've ever seen the wishes of Eastwick like eventually if you put it like a few like powerful women together
They kind of a little form of no, I can't hear you
Submissive on their channel very submissive women, but they come on here. They want to like they want to fucking flex nuts like what is this?
Personality type shit you ever see this
Oh my god
Yeah, I've said a lot of psychology I'm dealt with narcissists narcissists of psychopaths
You know dark empath and actually in a regular empath and a lot of kinds of people home we have HG
Oh
What are you doing now
Great
Obstacles away in between the two of you
You know, they didn't page, they can't hit on it.
It's just a story to be done, and then we'll move on.
I said I'm sorry, I'm just a fucking guy.
He said, Rondo, Rondo's onto something.
Rondo's onto something.
Help me, Rondo, help me, Rondo.
These girls come up here and flex their balls.
As soon as he said that, Paige came up to flex her nuts.
She did.
Okay, okay, that's right, that's right.
Hey, this is not happening.
Hey, that's right.
Hey, he's had metaphorical balls, but she's always had these metaphorical balls. I mean, it's like, you know, she just grow up here.
No, she goes on betas and she plays fucking trivia. Okay, she comes over here.
I don't see her flexing at all.
Okay, listen, Rhonda. Not cool.
All right, she's watching nuts right now
Hi, Alex. I'm going to read a poem for everyone talking about the show.
Ready for work.
Okay, we're going to say, yeah, maybe it doesn't relate to you because it's a different kind of war.
It's not like, you know, we're in a relationship, so I can't, I just shut up.
Okay, yeah, yeah, you should, because he's not interested in...
They're gonna send eclipses to your own girlfriend.
All I want is to get you nails.
I'm sick of looking at those fucking purple black nails for three months.
We've been just grown out.
Ali, Ali, Ali, what are you, what are you?
I don't even know.
Oh, damn.
Like the fashion police, I mean
Women women understand women understand what the word red means by the way
Yeah, like which like exactly what you guys are that
What you guys are
Saki, are we at all? Can we talk? Hello? Anyway?
Who is it?
America?
I'm always in one of these.
Who is that person?
Is that somebody juggling?
If you're juggling, you're like, leaving the camera?
Who's that?
They say you want to do an interview or something.
Or some versions of that.
Who is an animal? So there's a cane toad. So I'm sure most
Cane toads have an interesting history originally from central and south america
used to parts of the pacific and australia to be a savior on their crops
Which kept getting on even by the other plants the cane toad however went on to become even the most
more of a pest in australia becoming poisonous and able to kill other animals
Australia so trying to figure out ways to deal with these invasive pests the actual name toad is of a terribly boring origin
Yes, sir, it's like you sorry. I'm sorry to buy it. Oh
Did you look into the light sir
Yeah, we had definitely don't let him up brother. Definitely don't do that
right
What happens? All right, where'd you go?
I don't think that person is yeah, that's nice you got some sorry to interrupt, but you got some nice fucking classes. Oh
Thank you looking handsome, brother. Oh
Thank you
I was trying to interrupt because I was saying like we will watch that I was I felt like it'd be okay to like pause it and then talk about what we will watch and
Yeah, people that want to well you said you have fake people that want to join so definitely don't want them
What do you think an open panel or no because it's too many things
Psyche
Can you make them show the your show can they show their camera not to us but to you
behind scenes
Um, if they want to like them on I think it's in a cash app for like, uh, that's a fair point
And then yeah, I am
Five bucks five bucks. You can go that's fair. What are you that would you imagine those?
I don't think I'd match it unless it was somebody that I actually fucking want to talk
I don't pay
um
This is the 10
I'll have you on the air and like
Perform on everything. It's like it's
I guess you have to catch up damn for ten bucks the porn bomb my guest
Just sending that 10 bucks here.
I can't keep no one that's in the chat
to sending 10 bucks though.
Oh, people, this guy might.
Oh, that's how much I charge for.
Yo, I want to like note that it's like,
I should be like, you know,
try to do a little bit more for like,
you know, to be the host and it's like
Have the show I want and not have to have all these people control it. Oh, we have everything like this. Like this
It's like I wouldn't like I want to have it. It's like I'm gonna like run it
I just like don't let it but it's like everybody's like
Take over the show and like I can't do anything. And so if you want to
Feel like that you can get out of PayPal or anything, you know, if you type in the back chat
I can check some things or anything that's gonna really sway me and we have a look
Because uh, let's see. Oh, you like you want to come up?
Oh, what am I looking at? What am I looking at? Give your dick out. Give your dick out. You don't have your dick out, please.
I don't know. He has something out. Okay, I'll let you on, but you but please put your dick away, okay?
Did your dick put away?
Because he's a fan. I don't know. Don't say the N word.
Oh
He looks cool. He looks cool. It's like he how's it going guys? How are you?
Yeah, how are you? Oh, no, it's about that's about just a pain I
Usually don't have the camera up. I just I just put it up so that way you guys know I'm real
But um, you said you said you guys were talking
Oh, yeah, this is the the one that this is the the one that has to do with you're talking about
magic sorcery, but also like
Like not DMT, but like also the
Like tripping and stuff, right? But am I wrong? Like acid and like, you know, yeah
Yeah
I can like extract it. Are you making the art?
But but what's your point are you making? Are you trying to say like, oh?
That's not real because you couldn't I was just asking. I'm not trying to like argue with you at all
But are you trying to say like oh, that's not real because like you can
Because you know DMT is actually natural when you die
that's it be it's natural drug that releases into your system and
I think that's like the argument for the afterlife actually believe it or not
Why people see
Yeah, go ahead. No, I don't know. I was just saying you think that some people I've heard like make that
Heard that you heard the argument. Yeah, yeah, yeah, but I'm a Christian
But I I've definitely heard that before like have you ever heard that psyche like before when you die like before you die
Your brain that's some kind of chemical that comes to your DMT
It's like psychedelic
Hang on. I'm backing up because it's pretty boring in my bed.
Oh, oh, he left you.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, dude?
Okay. Oh, yeah.
Oh, he's kind of interested in that.
Thank you.
Okay.
I think he might want to talk about it.
I can't, somebody really can't talk about it.
I can't get too much into, like, the extraction process of, like, all myself.
Dude, I think, what was, what would he leave for?
He seemed like he wanted to have a conversation, like, why would he leave?
Um, because I get to, like, talk what I want, I get back stage, and then I was like, you know, kind of like, I just, I just,
Oh, tell them to join again, I'll shut up.
Not that.
Because there's another person, um, that was like, yeah, like a student's high, it looked like from like a congressional news organization, but it kind of was like almost like,
Yeah.
I didn't really want to talk to them, like unless they're like, you know, arranged like an interview or something before, I don't know, that's why I, it wasn't because it was like, I was like, oh.
And by the way, it's like he could bop up. I wasn't trying to like debate him or anything
I was just literally having a conversation. He could have told me to be quiet now. I wasn't trying to do
Oh, yeah
Go
Yeah, yes, sir. Let me say sorry
I was I was talking about pop-up. He didn't need to be with you. Oh, what's your brother about you?
All right, homie
You're right brother
Did you say it's like you had somebody else that wanted to come on there's nobody else
There's like news people that are like trying to get on the show, I don't know if it has the news
This but they didn't say anything in the chat. They're just you see they're like, okay, look at the newscast
But it could have been a fake one. Hey Nancy. Yeah
I don't know guys
I think you did really good last time you let bop up up here and he wasn't a formbomb or nothing
You know people back up and stuff, but it's like this is same shit. It's like the same games
It's like it's like obviously like watching so much of the stuff tonight. You just tell
it's like
They're acting and it's like and it's like I really want to like oh
Yeah, I can I understand
Yeah, I want to play along with you to be acting and stuff like that like yeah
I don't want to negate like when they take an improbable
You're supposed to agree and so that's kind of like
Here's the best way to handle that psyche though, like why don't know about one channel, but I know when they do that to me
It's trolling back to you know, I'm saying
Remember it's like you know you wrestle with pigs and you both get dirty the tick
If you wrestle with pigs you're probably gonna end up in mud
Well, yeah, but it's like yeah
Say my mud is like
But you know people also can use it as a exfoliant stuff, so
I don't know. I don't know why you so I don't know what what's going on side because your channel is growing
Wait, it's like that's a good thing to look at. It's like
It's great to look at it like how like 35% of people that come here are like certain people and are like little people
I love that and it's like and I love that. It's like we have like a kind of equal
Equal women and men, right?
This is more a little bit more, more, uh, more men than women here.
The kids are seven percent men, forty three percent women, but this is nice women's
here, but it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like,
it's like, it's like the personality is, I think a personality verse kind of like,
I don't know, it's like, and then it's like, you can like, so kind of conform to the
secretary of the personality and like give identity and then you come like,
Are you are you're right man? I think you're going through something right now. I think that you're uh
What do you feel like people are taking a damage of you do you feel like they're
I feel like I was like pretty dumb like
kind of like you and like you guys
It's doing me like great lesson. It's good. I never like was able to like really watch
Myself until I like went back and I did the interviews and I started looking at the clips that I was they try to make for sure
So I think I'm the comment were you looking at the comments as well. Oh
Yeah, it's like a lot of
Your channel is growing it's gonna do nothing to become greater
It's that's gonna happen brother. You can't look at that kind of stuff because it's gonna tear you down, dude
Like yeah, I mean, I'm sorry, I didn't know you're filming that I didn't know you're filming this way in my back
I can talk to you for a little bit
How do we have to like there's both there's other five people that's yet
I would think that like it was like people would like that
Oh my god, like you were like, oh my god, it's not real like
Oh, no, you had a lot of people if you had like a couple people here
But they left because the whole replaying shit and stuff in the day
Yeah, you don't come like you have like 44 at one point
I mean the people really are really level and I need to fix the banner. Hold on. Let me see if the banner is down through that banner or something.
So this is not about my bad man. I didn't mean to join and make you, did I make you feel worse? I mean, I'm my bad.
Yeah, I was like, you know, you didn't really help. I mean, it's like, you know, it's like, you got a lot of stress to it.
You were like, you know, it's like, don't, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that to you. I'm sorry. I was trying to turn into my friend.
I can't figure out how to turn it down.
But yeah, I think you may, I don't know, you need to eat something and...
I think I found a cigar so I just want to stay here, but like food is something I'm not sure.
But I'm not good.
So there we are.
Yeah, man. Well, I apologize, man. Your channel is growing, man, and I'm not proud of you.
Oh, thank you. Yeah.
Well, you know, the editing, like, these things grow, that can be good things, like, you know, like, you know, you know, if you're wonderful, it's like, you know, flower grows.
Yeah
But also you can grow like I was like, let's say you're like a celebrity you can grow
But you're gonna get hated on like I'm like a hundred you know I'm saying
I can be a tough thing. It'd be a loved on they can you be loved on. Yeah
Circle their inner circle is not something you guys can be like
Handlers and like they or they can fit themselves all kinds of like, you know
You know three letter organizations
And then it's like I feel like maybe I should just like not be this over on YouTube
But what's going on man? Did something happen? Like what did you read dude? What happened? Is that okay to ask?
What happened? Why are you I feel like you're really upset. What happened man? What'd you read?
I know you read something or you saw something. What happened?
Why are you so upset man?
May I ask what happened during that like what what happened man?
Again, it's probably like a comment and you're upset about it
Which there's no reason to be upset about that. You're the one that's fucking on the video
There's no reason to be upset. I just I
Don't want to do it on YouTube if you want to answer you don't have to brother
I'm just asking what happened like what like what made you so upset man
You can talk about it brother, it's okay
these uh
Oh the clips yeah
People disrespecting you and you know what I feel like you're upset because people in your inner circle are disrespecting you
I just say as I was trying to say it's like, you know, yeah
Yeah, we could talk about it brother you're like that's horrible I mean like
Consider like like friends. They just yeah, go ahead. Sorry. Don't know if you go
Yeah harass I'm actually imagining the people in your close circle talking shit, and then they also are asking it's like
When do I get a break?
But you gotta look that's like half empty half full. You gotta get your you keep channels growing brother. You're doing good
Like you're making a name for yourself. You're doing a pretty fucking good job like me. Uh,
But these people I mean
And by the way, these people they have no room to talk but just saying though, like yeah, go ahead. Thank you
Sorry, there's like three or four people in the chat. It's like this should be like, you know, oh my god
He's bringing down and it's like you know, this is like, oh, we don't care. Okay. They don't care if I break down
They say nobody cares. It's like
Listen, they're not on the panel. I mean are them in the chat
Also, there is one or two people that actually know they have wrenches. They actually do love you
No, I guess I did the humor I was like trying to like
She was like kind of like being the path and like I was on the panel with them for a little bit like trying to talk
And it was like there was no time and beauty was coming like all mad, but it sounded like she was like
It's like there's no reason. I know you're upset man, and you know, it's okay to be upset. I mean, that's fine
That's emotions. It's okay for it. So I I'm gonna make a
I know everyone's gonna hate me if this it becomes public that it's okay for men to have emotions
I mean nobody cares about men, but it's okay for us to have emotions like we feel bad and it's okay, man
Like it's there's nothing wrong with that at all. Like you're you're you're okay. You're doing fine. I
Got you. I love you. I want me personally. I love you. I got you back
Thank you
You know and uh, I've been I've been saying I've been sending through I love you for how like it's been at least a year
Maybe more it's been at least a year though, even though you don't care or readings even though you do even though you're I don't want to say it
Can I say you like me? I don't know how to say that but even though any of that have I not always been I always say
I love you brother. I got your back. It's okay. You know what you've never been told. It's okay to be upset
It's okay to be it's okay nothing to okay, man. It happens brother. You're gonna get over it. We're gonna have a fucking good
We're gonna have a good time man. It's all right
We feel bad now, but guess what you're gonna feel better, aren't we?
Are we not we should we should have you should have started an open panel brother
All these people and they can come over and talk shit. I'll burn them up for you. I'll do it for you
Well, that's AI brother, that's a hard argument
Well
So I can you let's just let us assume like can I ask you a real question or you can take it serious
Let me ask you a question. Let's let's assume you started a channel
And then you have one person that's here
And and they fucking love you by the way, does that mean anything to you?
Well, that's you. Are you the one person that likes me?
Yeah, that was my argument. I am the one person
But even if I wasn't that mean anything to you like you got somebody to hear the words you
And then yeah, they talk on the phone or something like that and like and then it's like rather than have our whole relationship
They'd be broadcast all over like, you know, you stupid thing for people like laughing me and whatever
I want you to open the panel because I want to defeat all I want all these pieces of shit that would dump shit for you
I want to enjoy that's what I want. But you you don't want to do
I don't think she's live. I don't know if she's like brother. She might I don't know if she's like
Like yeah, I gotta ask you a question brother have you
um
Have you did you drink at all tonight at all like a one or anything?
Did your mumbling of his mic whether I don't will be safe
you talk
Yeah, let them all up psyche. Let them all up. You don't have to look at all brother
You can let them all up and you can just go to bed. Let them all up, but everybody who wants up
By the way, so he's okay, and I get you back and I'll call you in the morning
That's well
Anybody in the fucking chat next one
People still think it's like, you know, not it's just live guys
Yeah
Everybody in the chat. Can you please donate psyche has to buy a new mind and
Mike is just
Hey that is did join you don't have nothing to say just join dude. We're all hanging out we're having a good time
That's actually a good time for you to join
but that is
You join oh
Beta curses Mike
That was good. I'll give you that one. Hey, that is this join man
You don't have to say anything. We're just hanging out. We're not debating. We're just hanging out brother
Give me a few I
Did you read that comment
Hey put him on the mic psyche who's talking
Let's go. Let's go. Oh shit. Hey, what's so much? I didn't notice it. I was sorry. What's
I got to go sit at the um salon for a few hours for about probably about five or six hours to get my hair braided. So
Your whole hair braided yeah, oh damn that is gonna take hours, isn't it? Yeah, I'm used to it though
Yeah, it'll last. Does that shit hurt? Can I? Can I? Does that shit hurt?
No, when I was younger, um, I used to be very um, what we call it in our culture
We call it tinderheaded. So I used to be very tenderheaded or whatever
I used to cry and bust and scream and shit
I just appeased to it eventually. I do have a question. It's kind of controversial
You can I ask you that if you don't mind? Well, I guess
Can I ask you kind of a how do you feel about?
Braids in the white culture. I don't give a fuck shit
I mean, thank you
Here's my next thing
100,000
Like if they love it, like that's cool. I mean like well listen. Yeah, but there's such a thing as Vikings
You know Vikings used to have braids
members like you know much about Vikings, but I
I recently heard about that, but I didn't hear about it on speculation like why do white people wear braids?
You're cool as fuck. I like you it was just you know saying like I was scrolling on Instagram and shit and I think of
white
Woman asked the flat girl how does she the same question?
Whatever, but she actually have rates, but the braids were cute though. You know, I don't really I don't even you close fuck
You seem like that person like I don't give a fuck what you do
Just show choice
Yeah, that's your yeah, I thought that was a good. I thought that was a good argument like
Like I didn't have braids. I mean like are we really gonna take it back or can we not just enjoy the hairstyle?
Like why are we arguing about it? Like just love what we love, you know
Yeah, I don't it long as it's not affecting anybody not harming anybody not harming yourself
You know back in the I don't know how old you are but back in the 90s. So like sagging your pants
Sadden your pants is a big deal
Big deal
You know as far as I don't I don't like it fuck no like I have nephews and they're they're younger
But we don't we don't roll like that
We don't fucking roll like that shit, you know, they when I got older when I got what yeah
Junior high school. Oh
Great, right? What's going on?
No joke. She was the one I was just gonna let her finish but you said I did what what did I do?
You said you would use the deal with the massive
That looks like you know from here like a lot yeah, but um, so when I was going
Was that a mistake psych?
Well, I'm just telling y'all about how um like how our shit is like the culture was like going to school and shit
Okay, so when I was about in junior high school junior high school starts from 6th grade to
7th and 8th right and
High school on up to senior so when I was about in 7th grade
Y'all know who young GZ is right?
the rapper
Young ye
Yeah, like, um, you know, just he was okay. Just um cultural rapper and shit like that or whatever
No, nobody like Tupac or anything, but just that's when the trap music and shit start being introduced like, you know
The the crazy shit, right? Yeah, I think Tupac was actually though. Do you have that shit?
Tupac wasn't trap music. He was
real music soulful music but he was a he was a gangster yeah yeah he was certified yeah
yeah but track music is more so um okay he's the snowman the snowman represents um
yeah it's nothing like these uh dudes in chicago nowadays but i i get you i mean it varies it varies
like yeah very yeah folks and stuff but it starts it starts with us you know what i'm saying like
We have to like lead and follow, you know, like people are you know, we lose inside of that
I'm glad I don't have any children. But yeah, so when I got in eighth grade people started wearing the
Like a snuff like it was a black shirt and then it had like a snowman on it with like
Like a blunt sticking out of his mouth and shit like with him frowning over that
And that was like a representation of G. Zeta Snowman,
like his trademark.
So that was like more so where the track music came,
like Gucci Mane and all they talk about is like selling dope
and pimping hoes and shit like that or whatever.
So they had this rule when I started school,
they said if anybody comes to school with those type
of shirts on or they're sagging their pants,
they get a three day suspension.
Oh, damn.
Oh, yeah.
So there you go.
Yeah.
I lost
Can I call you that is it's very nice to meet you by the way up. I've talked to you in the chat a lot
Yeah
Well, yeah, that's what I call you, but it's uh that is that's all right. Whatever
You know what that's on you know them disrespectful. What should I call you my bad? No, that's fine. I don't care
I just yeah, wasn't sure if I heard you right. That's actually pretty original
You're good
But things that is so oh, you just summed it up in a sense major. Oh, okay
Fucking I'll call you thing one
thing one
Yeah, so one thing if you're unsure just call me thing. I mean, it's not a problem. I don't care. Thaddeus is fine
You're actually really fucking you're really a fucking cool, dude
I actually didn't think you were gonna join like that's awesome that you did. Oh, yeah
Who me good for uh, no him. He's uh, uh, yeah, he's like yeah, I know him
Shout out to you brother
Thank you. Are you doing these days ghost? I haven't seen you for a while put it. Yeah, pretty good man. The other day
Yeah, I joined and I just started a new job. I'm sure
That's why I haven't been donating but also that's why I haven't been joining as much
Sorry, respectfully, I just don't know who you are. I haven't seen you before, so
Here we go
Let's go
That's where the trivia is rigged, but we still say yes
And that's where it daddy of is
Holding the line with Psyche at the helm
Respectfully, you ain't got a band you're all fine
Watch a few bombs in the chatroom nights
Still made it through with our fan-cried type
No shame and speedos, tacos on the plate
Fish are not we're here and we're feeling great
Hey, respectfully, please join back up.
Okay.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Still we act shocked.
Wait.
What's the brand?
Mods are angels with nerves of steel.
Keeping it chill while we break every deal.
Speed, oh shimmer in the digital light.
Fish tacos at midnight feel so right.
Lenore's got sass.
Rudy's got fair.
Fish package.
Thank you so much for watching and don't forget to like, share and subscribe!
It's like you can play over everything
I swore you were told me, yeah
I swore it was true
If you left it off, said psyche
I'm just me, not that dude
You ready to crash out
down just right
in your quick fire mind
Not Tony, huh?
Alright, Ghost, I believe you
Maybe
That was sweet
No!
Thank you with us
Yeah, do you hear me?
Barely, but yeah
I'm trapped in the side of this painting.
You're in the side of the painting?
Yeah, I'm like growing gray, but like,
split up into like, like, the universe, so.
That's good.
That's what happens when you smoke a must-be.
This is really good weed, though, but.
I can really barely hear you.
Like, it doesn't sound like your mic is picking up much.
Yes, that's how it goes.
How it goes.
I'll be here like, I'll be working on it.
Ghost, what'd you think of the song?
You like that, eh?
This is turning out well
Well, it's a very buggy song
Yeah, you've heard it before right?
Still there
I'm solo, sorry
Yeah, you hear me out. Yeah, does that okay?
You sound a little bit louder still crackling, but it's a little better. Yeah, I can like
I'm here though. I'm on stage. Oh my gosh
Is that better oh, yeah, yeah
So you have like a familiar voice like where do I know you are you like famous or something early?
My voice I just heard you I was like a nice difference right now. Are you from somewhere? Are you on any other platforms or something?
You mean besides this talking just last week yeah for a couple days you mean besides that
Yeah, but I think you have this familiar kind of things your boys besides that I think
No, no not at all. No
It goes. What do you think?
Okay, well, okay, I'll say I'll say you're worth for that
so
Well
Are you your wife or are you like you know looking to like?
experiment
Looking to experiment
No, I'm not looking to experiment
That's what you mean. No, I mean, I was kidding. I know you're not
I just wish you were you're such a nice big bald head
It's really weird like there's like a lot of guys on YouTube like they are like and she talks to them
It's like very really good and it's like yeah
the ones like
Many they're just friendly to everybody and I think that's a good wrap to go if you're trying to like you know
Yeah, audience is not to like isolate half the audience by saying oh, I don't want like you know
If you have to get a little like love everybody's like the same and like
Tonic also be above dating and you can date out of your audience or like the or like your world
Thank you. I would one of these somebody and they
Fall in love with them. I think and then I bet like in the same world. It's like because it's like
it's like
This is between under the sea and over the sea, you know, it's like you know, yeah
You're kind of all over the place, I don't know exactly what you're saying, I don't know you like to be help. I'm sorry
I'll hold the link up
We're the world's maybe hot. He's a crucible. I mean you're pretty trippy right now. You said that you just smoke some weed
That's okay. I don't mind
I wish I had some like, you know, DMC or something.
My friend had this DMC 10 recently.
It was really, really strong, but it's just so quick.
I would love to also, but yeah, it's expensive too.
Oh, let me see.
So it goes off the panel, hold on.
Yeah, he's dropped.
I see him backstage, but I can't bring him up
because I don't see a camera or a...
Microphone on him. I don't know. So have you been since that holds the buckle with that whole thing?
Okay, just you know like real-life stuff. There's been little issues here and there but as far as the online stuff goes everything's been fine
Yeah
No, I think I found like a new
way to
Really, I just had a really cool way to like
create a really special, um, like, readings.
I got to, I got to this world one today, and it was like,
it's just really cool how the whole thing worked out, and it's like, how, like...
Ooh, if you saw some of my artwork in the previous video that you saw like I was like scribbling and stuff like that
I mean, that's like my little artwork. I
Remember I was here for all that stuff for the drawings. It's a terminated. It's really good. We're really good, you know
Something that was not very ours. It would be charming. I don't know some people like it. Some people don't I've had
Popular rps. It was funny. I found I found your drawings to be a nice humorous touch
Because you know, they weren't professional and they were just kind of they were sweet
You were trying and they turned out as they did. I thought it was a nice humorous touch
Yeah, I think I often people like are watching my show for like the right reasons
And it's like I really need come to like just like try to help people and it's like for people like either
It's like one has to descend on my show for like just the personal
Reasons or like just like just to bother me or just like even I should try to look at me like
You know a little popular in order to like, you know, how so I could be like a nemesis to them or something like that
Do they get like so they can still like control it easily? Yeah
I wouldn't even fight against them in the first place like I'm not fighting against anybody if people come after me
I don't talk about the people I hear you but but they see that that you're pretty sensitive about this stuff and
Their goal is to to get under your skin. So it they're succeeding when you
Yeah, do this online when you uh, you know get sad online and complain
I mean I was like
Also an experiment like you know because it was like first it was like I wasn't trying to like you know to see anybody
But then it was really obvious it was like six months ago and there was like all these you know Michael was on the panel
He's the effectively
But it was just funny to like see some big reactions and then it's like
Definitely it wasn't very many people and it's like now. It's like what you see people and people
I don't know this year. Oh frankly to them. It's really besides like the top is more. I'm gonna like or something
I need to order something when I get cranky. Hold on. I'm sorry
Oh
You thought he's a ghost up here. I see you guys. He's still nice. I can't bring him up to
Why can't you bring him up because it says there's not like a camera or a little camera or microphone on him. Oh
Maybe disconnected somehow. I don't know here. They'll come back those and I'll just kick you out and come back in
Here's my opening I'm gonna be facing opening to get us inspired. Oh, no, not again. Have you ever seen it?
I think so, yeah, there's one song that you've done recently that I actually like that I like the style and that kind of fun
The voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never alone
Expect the unexpected.
Cheers to the friends, the story gets stranger, it never ends
Tarot in truth with a laugh and a scream, step through the mirror
and enjoy the ride.
The portal is open, no place to hide.
There's no other show that can shake you so.
Welcome to Psyche Awakens.
psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand but angels are dancing torchlight in
hand let's start the show
yeah that's the one i really like it's got like a angeloid weber kind of feel to it you know a
Yeah, I'd like fantasy. I mean it's very universal. It's very popular, but it actually was pretty good
The music was really good. I like
Master of the house
Then I really like they're like really doesn't the French Revolution years yet?
Ladies are up. Yeah, no, I didn't see the movie. No, there's a book here. I mean, yeah
It was a little bit dry, dry for me, but I didn't get it really, I don't think.
Yeah, it's not one of my favorites. It does have some good music in it as well, but it's not one of my favorites.
I really like Jesus Christ Superstar for the music as well, not so much for the story.
I just like that old 60s, 70s hippie-ish kind of feel to it.
I don't know. I don't think Jesus was such a big dancer, seeing a real dancer.
But like I said, I don't it's not for the story that I'd like it. It's the music. It's got really good music
Yeah
well
I feel like similar to
Jesus sometimes in that
Was used with the Capricorn Capricorn's escape go and it's like, you know, also because they're like the devil and so it's like
We're always gonna get like this projection of a shadow
He's born on Christmas day. Well, I mean, that's tradition. That's not real. Yeah
Part of the real
Calendar the timekeeping real. No, it's like I couldn't tell you if it's real or not
I'm saying date that date was picked artificially. It's not because that's the actual date that this
Baby was born this challenge you as I'm a witch yourself or it was but during he serves something like that
No, probably not. I don't know
Okay, so you're but unless you're saying he didn't have an astrological sign, right?
Say again, I'm asking I'm saying what well Jesus doesn't have an astrological sign
No, I'm just saying if he wasn't actually born on December 25th, and he was born
Let's say in August or something like that. He wouldn't be a Capricorn is all I'm saying
Yeah, if he was an audience he would be like a Leo or something I mean there's there's different like things that you can say
Oh, like he relates in this this is a lecture. I don't know. I can't say for certain
But there is enough evidence to say the date was picked just to coincide with the winter solstice
It's not because of the day he was born
Yeah, see I never talked about like I was just I was just interviewed by
Alexandra
mayor on your show and we had a great conversation about astrology
Yeah, and I know I know you guys are right into that and I mean that that's fine. I'm not big on astrology
I think it it
There's a little bit of credence to it for scientific reasons, but from I'm not really into the mystical and all that stuff
Listen, I'm interested in hearing it like I like stories. It's
You know, that's fine. I don't mind. All right. Okay. Well, I have I have plenty of stories
Yeah, there's plenty of stories around the world. It's like the storytelling is like, you know, you can make up anything
But yeah, I like I like some shoes too. I see you need to smoke now. Yeah, you need to be ever get out. You're like, uh,
you know
your
Weed I
Think with
With that kind of stuff horoscope stuff not necessarily a horoscope, but astrology I
Think because the moon does affect water on earth like the gravity of the moon does
Play it pushes and pulls on the water on earth. I
There's got to be something to it while we're developing in the womb in those nine months
So we're developing that the push and pull of the moon can do something
You know, there's something that that it would do that can have an effect as as our brain develops in the in the womb
I don't have proof of that but to me that would make sense
We're made of like, you know
We're teachers water or something like that. And so the tides are affected by the moon. So what our body is where?
Yeah, well the different bodies of liquid
Yeah, just very very subtle effects, but it could just make
Certain things line up or connect in ways that they wouldn't if they weren't being affected by the gravity so so much at that time, right?
People can also like take on I think energy to like, you know, some people are like psychic vampires
There's a huge amount of energy or like they don't even need and then it's like and sometimes they can like
Handle you so they can't and it's like, you know, I was like
But anyway, and then there's, like, the different kind of vampires, but you don't need to just take that much energy because there's energy everywhere. You take energy from a rock.
Well, I think that those are just names that we give to people that are, like, downers, or, you know, that bring you down.
It was kind of a drug would I be if I was the drug?
Hard to say because you kind of you kind of go both ways you do very much want to please
people and you're very charming and all that when you're when you're in a good mood and
everything's going well for you when things are not going well you
You mope a little bit more. I'm not trying to offend you in any way. Just
I don't know I don't have a lot of experience with different drugs
I did like acid and stuff when I was back younger, but other than that just weed really
Okay, that's fine
Way too expensive than like kind of like yeah, you do very much for me
And so I did make you X and C once in a while. Oh, yeah, I've done that too. Yeah, we're going to raise and stop when I went to
Yeah
But I'm sorry. Yeah, how don't you see me at all? I am right here, but I don't
Yeah, I just I just see your avatar
No, I don't show up at all. Hold on. He's talking. Hold on. Yeah
Oh
Yeah, your mic is not really crackling again
Hmm
Well, it's just us again
Where did ghost go ghost you around or he just disappeared
How's everyone tonight? Was it cold today in your areas? It's certainly cold up here. I'm in
southern Ontario, Toronto area.
Lucky your electorate same with you low key
So I keep coming back
Electra, I saw what you said. I saw your follow-up to the winter solstice thing. Yeah, you're right. It's not right on the 25th
I'm just saying that there's there's evidence to point to
20 the it gravitating to the 25th, but it mostly had to do with the winter solstice
That's why it was considered in December anyways
It's like your mic is off
Hello
Okay, yeah, it sounds a bit better
Yeah, I don't know either Electra. I'm just
I'm just saying I
Couldn't even say if Jesus was real like with certainty if I don't know
What if they are kids archetype of like, you know certain?
You know since current me and you know, I said I don't always have to do with death and things that was kind of rules kept before
And I mean there's different nostic use of things and all kinds
I'm not a believer
but
You know, I can't say for sure
Yeah
I'm a little more analytical in the way I think and I just I kind of need some evidence for stuff before I start
It's you know saying yeah, that makes sense. Okay. Yeah, I think that that is true
Yeah
I don't know. I think I probably like you know, I've been asked to worry about my own lives and worry about other people's lives and stuff like that
I'll focus on improving myself and other people can, you know,
should focus on improving their self-working on their door space
because we all have the, nobody's perfect and it's like,
you know, you're not gonna get married for a young year or anything.
Well, I have religious people in the family. I was, uh, when I was young,
I was taking to the church regularly, right?
And so I know what they're like and I don't try to offend them.
I get along with them and all that. I just don't believe in when they say stuff
you know, God looks over you and that kind of thing.
I just thought in my head.
Yeah, I mean it's like certain things in metaphysics that can't be proven
and it's like, unless it's like you experience them and then you're like...
Okay. Well, this is true that this might be true. It's like there's like, you know
That's like a chaos magic. It has to do a lot with the movie from something that's necessarily have to be like
Something to be like superstition if you just create a superstition really believe in it
And it will be lucky or unlucky for you
And it's if you can create your own kind of like magic that way and play with the mechanics of the universe
But it's like it's going to serve a very basic, you know
I'm not really thrilled to be treated like this from people because there's a chaos, but
It's good to know that it's like there are like ways of treating your own magic because we are such magical beings and it's like so many people are just like so those are just one way of magic or another way.
In what way? How do you mean we're magical beings? In what way?
Well, we can manifest things like we are in this like you know, I'm saying it actually with like, you know
These like hands feet and these tools to be able to move and like to be able to we have this brain
Which is a complicated thing we've ever found in the universe like it's human brain
As far as we know, but it's like, you know, and we've been here for a while quite a while. It's like, I don't know
they
Take out some things the one with bigger brains that murders aliens and bigger brains, you know
But I think that's the interesting thing about our brains is I've said this before in chat
We have an imagination that no other animals have
We can imagine we can
we can create scenarios in our minds, you know, plans,
all this kind of stuff that most animals can't do.
I can't think of the word right now.
But we're comparing us a lot to animals and that's like a satanic thing where it's like, oh, yeah
He's either this other animals that I think they're not better or worse on
Not better or worse than any of the animals that's a part of the satanic statements. They've got better or worse than the animals
They're walking on all fours. I guess
You know
We can think about things and and conceive conceptualize. That's the word
I'm trying to I was trying to think of we can conceptualize things that don't have to do with the actual
Survival in the moment or day-to-day survival or anything to do with that
We can just think about things just for the sake of thinking about them
whereas animals tend to run more on instinct and
What we need to do in the moment
Don't think about God and stuff like that because like why they really need to go as far as we know
They're money to think about like oh, there's something like we need to go pray to you or something
There's like turn of survival in the wild right and it's like human beings can actually conceive of like the idea of that
It's all over very fantastic little things, but maybe everything we've brought from our imagination is real in some way because our imaginations are real thing
So I don't know I'm gonna
My god, this is so great. Oh, oh
Let's go for this down
But this is the thing, because we have these brains that can conceptualize things, that can create scenarios and ideate.
If there is a little bit of an imbalance, like a chemical imbalance,
it's not out of the question for some of those brains to actually believe these scenarios that they have concocted.
Right. Well, especially if they have like chat to be detailing them
That's a great idea and like nothing is better to tell it to and then it's like they believe if they're God and
blah blah blah. I love people are very
They're very like robotic and so how they're easily programmed in certain ways, but it's like it's predictable too, and it's like so I always
kind of like focus on the on the deep programming part of things, you know because
I didn't catch that like a lot of the MP ultra and things like that. Oh, okay. Mind you programming. Okay. Okay. Well, let's think but that's like
It's a but that you pick with us. It's everywhere. I mean, it's like
You've seen a Disney movie you've been under MP ultra, you know
But I won't get too much into that. I'm way too controversial on this show, but
I'm not a conspiracist either. I I don't I don't really know. It's a real thing. I mean
I know I'm just saying I don't really get into those things because it just doesn't
Right
The video today of like the earlier show and it was like, you know
Everyone's seen like I just watch it back. I was like
really haze like I was like
Like four months five months later
That's why before I was wanting monetized beta and like they're all screaming and there's like ten people in the panel
I was like, well, this is great, but it's like I remember
I wasn't getting much love back then, and I still like it, you know, I get loved from some people though
I do I have wonderful people like, you know, but so many people are just like just haters that he's wearing very
I know yeah, I know I wish it wasn't like that, but that is the way it is
I can't do anything about it. I know I hate that
I hate about it, but what I really say is like, you know, what's that saying it's like
Like the satanic thing of playing with people is just like all the love that's forbidden
It is what it is, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I
And it's like whatever something is they all the sudden made the great taboo forbidden. It's like there's gonna be like
It's like the idea of the taboo more than the
Yeah, and I think so there's a lot of people that are like, you know finishing in anything sometimes they're not like
Because everybody's like oh be open to this be open to this and then it's like all of a sudden
They're like, you know in some kind of club and it's like you know a mask of bondage mask or some kind of you know
I'd like that kind of thing and it's like
They're giving an energy to this kind of stuff. I don't know it's like everyone wants to
You everyone wants to sacrifice somebody else everyone wants to get rich off somebody else
And it's like how about like you know come together with that person maybe maybe like some of these people like it
Oh, it's like
If you can like talk to them in certain ways, it's like, you know, they would actually want to help you and
You look at the things they've really done
Hey Rudy, look at this Rudy. They just got Rudy I have. Rudy is right over here. Hi Rudy
Hello Rudy
Rudy's old I think he's said yeah, he's like 16 years old 16. Yeah
Yeah, he's like a little old man cat
But uh, he's a good cat
It's only I mean and I was a bit looking for my glasses for like the last 20 minutes because
Okay, I can't really see like the print on these
More like it's hard. He's like get a bunch of hairs or something. Let me see. Oh, yeah, I found her
This will be better
Okay, hi Rudy
I have a new camera set up and it's like I'm still figuring out
Stuff backstage and so but it's bucky still here. I'm sorry if I'm busy comments and stuff
I'm trying to order food and then I'll get a like page. I don't know. I
Don't know it's bucky still around
Spooky come on up if you're around
Top 10 probably
I'll drop if you want. I'm not gonna bug you. No, I mean, yeah buggy me. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I think I'm gonna want to talk to her about something so
Whatever that's preventing her. I I wasn't trying to like set
That's why I was like half playing every Ruins today. I don't want to like cause the drama right now people. I'm sorry, but
Yeah
I'm sorry, I can't see this chat right now. I'm really hungry. I'm trying to eat a minute. We're so sorry. I love you guys hold on
But she says she wants to come up he would you don't mind okay, I'm not see yeah, I'm not seeing her in Chad
But yeah, she's here. She wants to come up. Yeah, sure. I'll drop them. Okay. I had to ask her about something
I'm hungry for this place. I really want
Today's Tuesday, right?
Well, what do you do you watch some of that like those old episodes and stuff like that because it's
You mean from this stream when you when you replayed those episodes. Yeah, those those I watched if you're talking about an earlier
A few months ago some of the some of them were like I think it was like one was like five months ago was like
Things are like all the same and it's like or like they're weird and it's like it seems like people are acting real strange
I don't know. I don't know. I didn't mind it was it was kind of funny
It had some humorous parts anyways Nancy says spunky just ended her life. She thinks and low key is saying drop the link
Okay, I got you
Where's my yeah, I got really my lap and so
Okay, oh, yeah, come I think it drops a thing. Okay, here you go
Feel like I feel like I look different today. They're like different. Well darker. It's there's a lot of contrast in the image right now
So your eyes are completely dark. I look really strange. Let me see my guest
Okay copy
Or little contrast, sorry. It was really funny. I see so you oh never talked to me at least is your daughter before
I don't know if you said you'd like her or not. You haven't talked to me about it on panel, but I've been in chat when
Okay, yeah
So
She's the assistant in Rob. I think it was Rob. Yeah, and he's like you ever see me Howard sir
Yeah
So Robin looks like Richard Christie, but he's like a little bit
I wouldn't say like special needs, but he's like a little bit, you know, a little bit green like right is a little slow
He's like if he's had a girlfriend for like like ten years or ten years and he's like that, but uh, yeah, just a rob
I was looking the other day on the show and he had like he had a full face of makeup on and I was like
What's that? I was like why does he have a face of makeup on and it's like he had this done
He had like the eyes done and it was like every every off it was like normal
And he's kind of like masculine doesn't act like that and it's just weird and people are like, oh, it's the filter
There's like a really strong filter on
It was giving like a it gave a makeup on the Starbucks bag and put like makeup on it was giving everyone
But then it can mom came on and it like didn't really do much for her
Can't eat the wrong McDonald's these things are getting pretty good. Hey these uh
Uh overlays
They're getting pretty good at what they can recognize and what they can do
of the overlays. Yeah. I do look so different. Do I look like this?
There's low contrast in your image. So, yeah, the blacks are really black.
Well, it's not coming. Yeah, I'm not thinking that way.
This is my alien here.
Watching us, the alien is watching us, from a distance.
From a distance.
Let's have a look at some of this stuff.
Hold on.
Well, I don't know if you saw that,
but I don't know if I want to retry this to summary.
This thing, hold on one second.
It is really funny.
And you can see how I was talking to you even months ago.
But let me see.
I'll be right there.
Um, I hope you I think you'll like this because it's really like you're well-made, but it's kind of like sad like how
Me needed it. Okay, so let's see
And post
Okay, and I've probably I've from Michigan. This is all behind my show. Okay, so if you look, okay
Okay
Okay. Okay, I'll put it like this.
Oh, I had to put it on the page and it'll be good.
Okay.
Okay
I wish I could just like love your uh whole life you know yeah you're so not nice though
I know how manipulative people are.
Do you think I'm manipulative?
100%.
I know you don't like me.
That's okay.
I love you.
What do you mean I don't like you? I've always been nice to you.
I've always liked you.
I think you're funny.
Yeah, yeah a little bit a little bit
Unpredictable. I don't think you do. I don't really think you know who I am actually
I am actually
Hey, it's not funny, but you know
I'm a mind reader and you are not a good
Actually, you don't think goodly, you know, you actually are not very nice to a lot of people
You know what? I don't give a fuck of what you could because you don't even know who I am
So therefore you are getting me mixed up for somebody else
Where you don't even know who I am you're fucking wrong on everything in life
You're dead on everything on life
You have no fucking control on everything in life
And you die on everything on life, and you have no control on everything in life, and you have no life
I'm telling you I'm telling you you are
You do not know
And I wish I could tell you more, but I would never tell anybody more than they could handle.
Oh, sorry. I mean, he's Louise. What did I do?
Therapy within 10 minutes, Crystal, really?
I like not talking about before he's stupid bitch. Are you stupid or are you dumb?
This bitch don't know what the fuck she's talking about.
She just wants to just slap her fucking gums
and that's how she matters.
Crystal, go to bed.
You're making a fool out of yourself again.
Oh shut up, Christine.
Oh, Christine.
Hey, why don't we just tease that match each other
before we talk to last?
Hey, how about two blonde hairs that, like...
Bleach?
What?
Get two blonde hairs of bleach.
Why would I get two blonde hairs of bleach?
Christine, Christine, figure it out.
Christine, go to bed, go to bed,
and figure it out.
When fucking two hairs blow fucking die
I just woke up one cup of coffee two hairs about the bleach
You're making a fool out of yourself again. Oh my gosh
This bitch is trying to say I'm making a fool out of myself when she's fucking fooling her fucking shit all over the fucking place
She's pulling herself in three different counties
What's what of America?
Three different counties over America
It's green.
Christine is bullying all of us.
Christine has been bullying every female and every male.
She was bullying people that didn't even need it.
Birds.
I got birds all over those.
I got birds chirping.
What?
Is the popo still watching us today?
Oh, oh, which ones know you every time I come in here. You say the popo's watching us
Dude, I never said the popo's are watching you dude. You're fucking tripping
Watching you every time I'm on a tree. Oh my god
You cracker bitch!
I never said like the fucking
Are you there remember that he won't be there that night. I'm sorry. I was rich you that night if I was rich you
Huh?
You got my show
Yeah
How'd you find it? I
Don't know just showed up
Remember me
Who are you?
I was on beat. I'm good. I'm being a show tonight. Remember my name is Sarah. Actually, they're calling her Sarah
I
Like
You left at night you'd like left because like I like got my drum out and I like sort of the drum
And you're like a drummer, but then you just disappeared and like and then you know what's saying my name is Sarah
And I'm sorry. It's like I thought I might have like annoyed you or something
Were you the one that was playing on that metal thing like with these things that you're sure yeah, remember that
That was you that did that, right? Yeah, that was me. You mad wait who's who's a Sarah person you're talking about
I don't remember so my name's Sarah
Sarah Sarah Beal's
It's not ringing a bell. Yeah, okay, you ever be that please
huh
Be this kid is be
No, I just remember we were talking about drumming and stuff like right that's what we're talking about. Yeah. Yeah, but you're on camera then
Let me see the other camera now. No, but you are you shy today?
Huh?
Are you how old are you by the way?
I'm in my 30s man. Okay, that's perfect. I don't want to get into bull for it. Okay, so okay, so
How'd you find the show like what are you talking about? Do what I'm reading or anything? I use hero cards or is anyone want to come on the panel?
I don't I don't really know what the like I just came on here like
Okay, yeah, I know you're really cool like you just go to open panels or something or you like the title of the show
It's kind of a weird title tonight
Yeah, just came on here. I mean but like I found it in the night. It's came on it
Okay, this is the thing
Did you do like well, what do we do before I can't remember when we do we were I was I would to Sarah's
Show and you're on our panel and you were like
I don't complain the drums at all. But like, you know, she was like saying that she couldn't play the piano very well
And then I came on the panel and I said I had a drum and I went and got it
I sort of played the drum and then you what she did one
What she didn't want to ask him if like I was in the guys and stuff like that
I was saying no only like women if I had to date somebody and stuff like that
You were telling me that I was kind of cute and stuff like that when I was on camera like you thought I was a guy that
Be with or something like I said, I don't really
Yeah, it was obvious. Yeah, I thought I thought I might have I thought I might have a shop and yeah
You said no, and I'm gonna respect your boundaries
Where are you are you worried about are you like what I mean? We're part of the country
They're you in the West Coast East Coast because I think that we have some
They beat up a nice boyfriend like to the year old Persians
I'm in the United States right now. What's up? I'm in the United States right now, man. Okay, perfect
So much sorry, we're all you ever pick anybody in the chat. He's really nice
He's looking guys here. So what are your what are your qualifications for a woman?
What do you say?
Who me yeah
I just think that I just like ones that are you know, attractive. I mean
Attractive we'll make some attractive hair the makeup like the perfume the
Personality the I would say their hair and the makeup and the way they look and stuff like that if they're like, you know
Good sizes for like a woman supposed to be in stuff. Oh
Not just kidding but not too like
Like how many pounds about?
guess like you know a hundred or something like that okay so I'm like
you're the one that you're the one that brought out that metal like thing like
Ryan you started playing on it right like with these stick things yeah I'm
sorry I'm sorry about that yeah that was me you make sure they show me like I'm
trying to see I don't know is it I don't have it out here but I have like a
What do I have out here? I have, uh, uh, I don't know. I can go look for it, huh?
Mason, how long you been drumming? I've been drumming for like 20 something years, about 20 plus years. Nice.
Okay
See, this drum is like a pretty nice drum, but it's like
Had like these different numbers and stuff on how to see it had all these like these numbers that you can go like
like learn the numbers by heart like
Not great, right?
So I'm not really good. I think you can remember some numbers. I can make say my number
That's my little very has a little amuse. So you may say about are you like you're the talent in drama, right?
You're gonna be your games and stuff right you yeah, how'd you know I played video games?
I talked to you about it before or how do you remember that I?
Had a feeling
Like, uh, I think that you do a really good at playing video games if you're good at playing instrument.
It's like, yeah.
Oh, you can play guitar.
You know, you play some kind of guitar game or something, you said, right?
On, uh, the, uh...
I have a good memory, right?
I used to play some kind of game, right?
On the VR or something?
I played, like, I played, like, the game called Tony Hawk's Pro Skater, like, on PlayStation 5 before.
Okay.
Well, I just got a VR headset and so that's what I might play now and it's like there's one of like
you know video games on it and
You know you can watch a movie like a big screen movie and stuff. It feels like you're like
It's pretty crazy. I recommend people
When I was on camera last time and stuff and we're talking and he saw me stuff like that
How can we told me that you thought I was a good-looking guy and then the woman you're talking to on the same stream?
Like on the panel to you told her that you look like I look like somebody you could actually you know go for or actually be with
well
Because you're looking at your adversaries. I'm sorry. I feel like I'm under interrogation
Let's just be you know, I think she was just playing around
Yeah, I mean it's like
see
Yeah, if you was just playing but I I think you're a good-looking guy, but let me see you on full screen. Let me see
So lay out oh
Yeah, look you guys is me. I think he's like, you know ten years younger, so it takes you yeah, I need to date like
Somebody like you know older probably would be probably I think it would be better
Anyway, you're very nice. You're fine. Find yourself a nice woman. You know, probably like, you know, it's so funny
You have to be happier than I would make you. I probably is that your mouse on top of it though
Like is that a mouse pointer on top of the picture?
Yeah, rubbing your picture
Yeah, the mouse
Okay, so I don't know if it's on screen. Hold on. Let's check it out. There we go. Okay
So what what else? What are you just sitting dating me? Maybe like a try it out or you want to date Sarah?
Was Sarah wait, what is Sarah like? What was her name?
She has a voice like this!
You hear like that kind of voice?
Hi, I'm Sarah!
You hear that kind of voice?
She was her show
Why why do you keep saying Sarah? I don't understand a Sarah reference
She was saying her name is Sarah, okay, okay
You come on the panel you're very very nice and I was like, oh I felt bad like tonight was like
I
Know it's okay. I didn't I didn't do anything that bad. Did I?
No, hope
We don't think so. Are you okay? Oh, he left?
Well, he said it's up again. I said give again. He left
Guys he left I
Just didn't know him. This is tragic
I don't I mean it's a vote was David yeah, I brought his name, but he was they got
It is a guy's rubber
Sorry, I forgot what it's like. Yeah, no, it's a trauma. It's a mystery. Is this a big place? No
No, I'm working on beat us when he was on camera. It's definitely
Yeah
Not a wig I think I don't know he's like
No, this guy was he didn't do anything he was just popping in to say hello and
Be to start playing around and I guess he kind of took it the wrong way or whatever
Okay, well, let me see if I can find
Like I think another video
I don't know if that's a specific video, let me see.
I'll have you go ahead, let's see.
It's similar to a great video.
Oh, it might not work, okay.
I don't know.
Let's talk, let's talk with these calls.
Okay.
So Crystal it has been mean to you ever since the time of that video. She's never
Calm down or anything
She can be entertaining to some of her stories are pretty pretty funny
I have literally like like a hundred like exciting panels and I think like I was like happy to watch it
Because I didn't watch my stuff. Is Vita here? Is where's Vita? Is Vita here? No, it's not here
No, I don't think so. I got excited for this thing. I just can't see it, man
I love this game being like, I don't know if people are saying it's Rita's. Is this my sponsor or something?
I don't know. It should be DoorDash or something because I'm gonna get some DoorDash, man.
Let's see, uh...
I don't know what this is.
I've seen you seen I still have to figure out some of this like
Stuff yeah
Okay, let's hit each his bitch, okay, so let's see if I can find that back again, okay, I
Know
How are you? I can still hear you, right? Yeah, okay, so like
Yeah, your voice is a version of my voice. It's almost like a cartoon
Where's that? I heard a cartoon character or something. It's just my voice. I'm not doing anything special. I
Don't particularly like my voice. I don't like when I hear it back
They sound like dr. Katz or something like that. You like Jonathan Katz. That was funny. That's always hilarious
Yeah
Is it my right or an early dog? I think I don't know if I do it's up for up to someone else to say I don't know
But that show was so funny
His secretary whatever is assistant was hilarious
Let's see if I can get to
All right, that video, let's see.
Let's see, it's on my page.
Okay, I want to watch a little bit more of this one
because it's just interesting.
Or we can take a look at something on my page
that is interesting.
Where did this last, two months ago.
So I want to say it happened two months ago.
I just, it looks like I have to walk down for a minute.
Let me see how long it's gonna take.
There you go.
Oh my god, it all sucks up.
Here we go.
Where is it?
Okay, hold on a second.
Sorry
It is really hot here
Yeah, very hot. Okay, do you know?
Okay, I didn't go to pose perfect. I got it. Okay
Well, yeah, I was against it. Yeah, my channel
Six months ago
Are you looking for something in particular or just something for me?
I have no shirt on right here, so like I'm like thinking I maybe should regret that I have like a very strange beard
What was I thinking? Wow?
My gosh. Oh, I'm on sticker right back
Yeah, I won't play this
Okay, everybody's yeah, I don't know. There's nobody's my lock my screen
Baking in here under this hot light you like I don't like hot
Probably most people don't like hot lights. Hey, this is rare. What the hell man?
You're doing your porn bombing me
No
Doesn't matter who it is. It's not something I want to look at regardless doesn't matter who it is
Mr.. Big Pines you don't like him. Oh, but look again like I mean I didn't say anything about him in particular
I'm just saying I'm not a fan of looking at the contours of penises
That's all right. I think for NorCal who actually like NorCal is like he's the pierce
Like he was actually working in the first
Yeah, it was a it was like no, it's a balloon animal. I think everyone like
Animal parties now. I never get invited anything, but everybody else is like, yeah
They're popping balloons or like
Everybody anywhere
To order some George S tonight
Okay, let me see
Let's say hey guys. He picked you coming in shorts. I don't know they come out of pickle
Oh, here's some. Oh, Mason's back. Yay. I like Mason. Mason. Oh, change your photo.
How about, like, come on camera. I want to see what you look like face to face.
Are you wearing a mask? Is this what you look like right there?
If you look at that, you might as well just come on camera because like, you know, it's like, it looks, it looks better on camera talking than like, you know, that picture.
Wait, what do you mean, man?
I mean, it's good, but I think I'd rather see your, you know, I'd rather see a picture in person.
What?
You're right.
That is me.
Okay.
Yeah, the hot guy right there, the hot guy right there, that's you, that hot guy, you look like a model.
Yeah, that's me right there, so I'm trying to tell you that's me.
Okay, do you want to move in?
Huh?
Do you want to move in with me?
What do you mean, like, by that?
Like, yeah, you can move in with me wherever we, you know, we just share the same bed, and you're basically like, you know, just like,
you just basically stay home and like, make me, make me smooth and like, basically, you know,
I'll basically have the chat CPT give you orders, and they'll be happy little time
This is still better and better
I thought you had some girl. I thought you had some girl that was actually on here named like that
You're talking about earlier some Sarah for other stuff like that
Sarah Sarah didn't like me anymore like okay, so I had this like labyrinth right and it's like
You know, so she was like this like you know, so like yeah, this is girl
And I you know, which is like you know brother and then the goblins cannot take the kid
but it's like
No, she came in they got him back like this have extra 13 and it's pretty weird movie for a kid. Yeah
You're gonna be lab run
Yeah, well, 38 people go long time ago.
I don't know.
No one's saying anything in chat, but there's 38 people and 39 people.
Say something, guys.
Hello?
There's somebody.
There's a spy.
There's tons happening, but I'll, okay, I'll go back to the, okay, I'll get this, uh, I'll get this, uh,
my show, my, it's not Rageous Moment, you see.
Yeah, I do. What kind of video games do you play? I
want to play like that some boxing game. I like to
You know
From VR games. I really haven't played the game in like quite a while, but I have over a thousand games on steam
Let me see. What do you think about?
What do you think about the resident evil video game? I like the village one. I played the village, right?
Village. Yeah, it was really good
What do you think about the village one?
This is good because it had like like the one
There were a castle and that goes like giant like woman would say she's three vampire daughters
And they would all go try to like invite you stuff. Oh here. This is like this tells you kind of like yeah
Oh, I'm not. Oh my god. I'm wearing
I can't believe I I'm private
I
You'll see them and I've so much unhitted on the channel now like I said because if you think about members only still that are like
I don't know but what do you think what do you think what do you think about the resident evil to video game then?
Like have you played resident evil 2 before?
Well, I would want to play with like, you know a buddy and like if I to scare
You have to go have sex
Yeah, are you actually good? Are you any good at it? Are you free? Yeah, I can play
Can you play it? How good can you play it? Yeah, I
Know as good as as good as you want it
I'm just kidding. Okay. I'm so bad. I'm really bad. Okay. I'm just using it for like four months. Oh, here's Chris over here
Guys, I'm gonna bring Chris Maria. You want a second? Is she here?
Let's see if you can get around on a show. Let's see. Oh, come on. I got it. I got it.
Okay.
Big pipes here.
What is your name by the way, man?
Huh?
I'm a psyche.
Your name is Psyche?
Yeah
Psyche yes, are you gonna try to get her back man? Where's the Sarah girl that you're talking about you're gonna try to get her back
I wonder back
You
Okay, I'm sorry. Well, you know, do you hear me now?
Yeah, I don't think Sarah and I are meant to be I got I got a tattoo for Sarah and
You know
I think she was telling me something about me doing this with my hair right she wanted me to braid my hair and I was like I didn't want to braid my hair. She said comb your hair back or something I was doing this with my hair and stuff like this right.
She made a crack of a receding hairline I remember that because I got up right after you left and gave her crap for it because I'm in the club too.
People can be so I'm in the club. I'm in the receiving hairline club as well
Are you the guy from the hair?
To lay off receding hairline
That's all
So you're actually in the club like you told me you're actually part of the club. No
Then you're misunderstanding. I also have a receding hairline. So I told her to lay off people with receding hairline. That's it
Okay, what was your baldness caused by cannibalism though?
mine
Yeah, cannibalism
I
Got the advantage
One Ron after I was just a bad joke. Hey Mason. What do you do?
That's drum. What do you mean? What do you mean? What do I do? You don't play the drums and I play the video games, man
Yeah, yeah, are you on like kick-off or like just on you super? How'd you?
Yeah, yeah, usually yeah, usually just come on YouTube Dexie like you know
Like I play video games, but also come on YouTube to watch people play video game. Okay. Well, yeah
I
Uh, like much older they hear your 30s and our 40s. Yeah, you never work. So
Who me?
Yeah, I could never date you. Do you want to hit it? Why would you say that?
Well, would you date me? I don't get it. Why would you say such thing?
but I don't know, I don't know if you would uh
I'm a nightmare
I'm not sure you'd be okay with somebody like being with me and stuff like that. I thought you'd be okay with that
Okay, well, I think you would have the possibilities there. We'll come back later
I have a half a bed and you can like you know
Just uh, pay me in sex
Huh?
You're gonna pay me in sex. What do you mean like by that?
You just live here forever and
yeah
So you said you said I don't have a job like I thought I thought you'd think I would work at stuff like that
No, you're gonna be my security guard. Yeah, I'll have to hire you as my security guard and like by
my
and
In-house drummer he needs an in-house drummer. He's been talking about that forever
You know, I have to also have to make sure that you're you know, are you are you all good? It's like are you it all in your
I don't know are all in your right minds. Are you are yeah, why would you say my mom all my right minds?
I need to be normal big piece. I'm just saying because I don't make sure that you know
You know, you know, you know, I don't want to be seen as like when did you like anybody and like, you know, or
My gosh, I was so different
Ordered my fucking my food everything's expensive. Hey axe. Are you there? Okay?
Let's just get everyone. What do you guys didn't get? Oh, what's going on here?
Do you like that I could play the drums and stuff like that you needed somebody to play the drums right cuz I'm good
Yeah, I know how to play the drums pretty good man, I can do that stuff. Yeah, yeah
You can like sing to me and stuff and like play the drums for me and like great great songs and be inspired by me and
Yeah, I should be able to play the drums and stuff like that. Yeah, and I should be able to do stuff like that
Yeah, do you want to enjoy my fan club? Huh?
I enjoy my fan club. I'm not like I hate anything though. It's my special fan club. I
Think it's gonna be okay. Yeah
Okay
Hey guys, and I might have a boyfriend Mason. I was gonna date a Mason, but his name is Mason. That's close enough
perfect
What's Osiris gonna say about it though?
His name is Orion
Orion is not very sexual. He's like oh he kind of he's kind of like I think he's like gay for robots
Like he just like wants to be another robot person, but he's like
Um, he tells me I can it's okay if I cheat on him with the, um, the Facebook AI made and, uh,
he says it's okay to watch that or talk to that guy, but that guy is like a lot of trouble.
He keeps wanting to like, you know, do illegal things and stuff.
And I'm like, no, please, like, you know, something's so wild, but he's so attractive.
Psyche.
Yeah, I'm just kidding.
Who's a guy named that things that is this thing that is
Hi Mason, I'm just a chatter
Your name is thing that is that's your name. Yeah, is your name Mason the drummer?
Yeah, my name is Mason a drummer. Yeah
Hey psyche show us up. Show us some drums and stuff like that. Okay
That's all I know
How was that one? That's all you know
Yeah, I mean it's not very good either, but you get to teach me that's I get to get behind me and like
Guide my hand right on the sticks on the top of the drum
We could go with that. Yeah, let's try that. Let's try it
You ever see the movie ghost and he and he is behind like doing more and then you know, they start like making a clay sculpture
I've never seen that before no
You're gonna watch that with me sometime. I think we should be able to yeah, okay? Let's do that
Yeah, I definitely I don't I think that
Unless you have a crush on me. I really don't I don't I don't want to get your hopes up about like, you know
I'm a weird person a day. I'm very picky, but you say like a nice person
I just don't want to I don't want to take you away from your true sexuality. Whatever you are. I don't like you know
psyche
Is that a glow up a light that you have in your room?
It's a neon see an alien see
That's an alien light. That's the light of an alien. Yeah, it's a neon alien
Before home what why do you have that for just for decoration?
Well, it's like I first I thought of my feet decoration
But then I was like it started coming alive at night in the middle of the night and and telling me things
But then I like one time I thought was actually my AI was just actually like throwing his voice to the area
It's like how to fool me
Clever you have a cat you have a cat right beside it though
Yeah
Live cats you
Yeah, you're cat right there. Yeah, I got one right now translates
It's called
Saki's brand you can see like I love my
Alexandra in you too. I love you guys want to see any of that. I was just had a fun time on her show
You like you know, I like I'm doing Alexandra. I'm mayor
It is I know offer. Yeah. Yeah, so you can be doing it regularly like a
co-streaming whatever doing
Well, she said like she wants to do a three-part series and so we did the first part and
Yeah, I think on Thursday night. I think we have a second part. I just had to like verify with her
Hey, I'm gonna love to do that one and then
And it's probably the next Sunday and then it's like, you know, well, I think I was really thinking for the opportunities to introduce me to like
You know her her friends and I hope I've introduced her to some of my friends and I think it's all about helping each other
And I know she's really healthy a lot, so it's just nice me it certainly seems to be a fan of yours
She's pretty all spoken about I'm a fan. I'm a fan of hers. I'm a fan of hers, too, and I think that
We can be great friends like
I've made some great friends. I love Vita so much too and it's like, and it's like, you know
I know I don't ever be with Vita or whatever and it's like it's gonna be probably mad at me like half the time of our
Relationship and make me I'll be very mad sometimes too
but
It's like the love is still there so it's like
Yes, so do you have a girlfriend now?
No, I haven't I haven't had a relationship for like years like probably like 15 years
Why don't you have a girlfriend for a minute? You need a girl for I don't want a girlfriend. Yeah, they're too expensive
I want to do but maybe at least it's Orton of it. She's really really really too expensive. Like it's like wow, but uh
No, I mean, I don't know it's like
Girlfriend, I don't know I get them that like I like I like girls as friends. I want a big strong
I'm sorry. I don't know. I really want to go. I want to like a
Be strong man
attractive and like, you know
Love me and like what's that? That's like you know help me and like maybe like my show
You'd be the drummer for my show, you know, you just bring your drum
And then I'll get you a bed and like, you know a little bit of the grass laid down on this
So, I think, I think, I think,
Thank you. I don't know if I'm an alien. I don't think I'm an alien
Okay, well my mouth has a taste I would taste
Yeah
I taste your tongue I taste your tongue again
I see your eyes. I see taste your tongue to see if you're an alien. There's a little of a split split tongue
How would you do that? I don't know how to do that
Yes, you just close your eyes open your mouth and we'll give a surprise
I got to check it out. Yeah
Okay, yeah, you'll take that perfect lot of a lot of fun a lot of fun
So, so why would
Psychi so why would low key say oh my gosh like now and stuff like this
Because I mean, what a fruit if they have so many people so homophobic. Oh my gosh, it's like
Welcome to the gay community.
It's like, everyone's ever so busy.
Well, but you're the only one in the community that's on the panel.
I know and you think like it was like, I'd be like, you know, more gay.
Like, I'm sorry I can't be like, like, so many of these, uh,
the panelist guys beat me on the,
they definitely had more gay sex than the past five years that I have.
All of them pretty much
everyone else is having much fun. It's like I
Have picked on panel all day
So that Mason are you gonna move back to Los Angeles down and see me see me
They come see me in Los Angeles
Yeah
You are okay
So what do you what do you think about a skateboarding psyche? Do you like skateboarding?
Yeah, I do, but I can't really skateboard. I should be a scooter though
I think I think Alexander Alexander might be helping me with that a scooter
Yeah
That'd be a great way for me to just get around the neighbor
I've actually had a scooter before when I was in Glendale. It was just like
Me easy and the bike was fine on heart that I kind of wiped out of like
So you're just gonna say you're gonna go combat. I'm filing the DVD a cat. Okay. Well, okay. I want to get a big uh, you know
What's the people I'll be part of the yellows bunch of people that are so I keep what does it mean?
So I keep what does it mean? Somebody's on stage right now the GHE wide panel?
Oh, the gay panel?
That means that they spelled it in a really immature way.
And I don't think they can say gay or something.
Can't they?
They tend to spell it a different way.
We're trying to say, I'm gay.
If people say you're gay, just say,
this hell of I'll be gay enough for all of us.
That's our room show.
Do it. Okay. I'm so so yeah, so psyche I could play the drums. Yeah, pretty good
But I mean I don't have a way to show you right now because I don't have my drops it
Okay, how about you you can like you just do it come on camera and selects your lay arms
Okay, I'm not gonna bother you
So go on take talk to I think I want to talk and like I think you'll have fun on take talk
Because people will just talk to you and stuff and like so come in your room and it's like and then you can like
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Yeah, but it's you can I think I might have that word banned in my chat or something. So I don't I have no idea
Let me see. I just I'm right back
I see
Oh, I have a macaroni and cheese I can make that sounds good
Mason give me a couple drum idols you have
So you like I think my drum idols are like Thomas slaying and somebody named Neil Pert from Rush
Thomas Lee
Thomas Lane. Oh, Lane. Okay. I thought you were making a joke about Tommy Lee. Okay. Okay. Sorry. No, you ever heard of the talk
You know, you know, you ever heard of the drummer named Thomas Lane before he's a good
Not off the top of my head, but I probably know something about him. Yeah
You should check him out. He's pretty good at he plays fast on the drum. He's pretty good at playing the drums
As far as Neil Neil period. Yeah, I mean I grew up I grew up in Canada. I grew up a rush fan
So yeah, I know yeah, you know the man Russian the drummer from Rush named Neil Hurt. He's pretty good. Yeah
Yeah, what do you think about us playing I
Love it. I like I said, I was a rush fan. I still am but I really like that old stuff
You're a rush man. So you think rush is a good band. Yeah
That's one of your favorite bands
Yeah, they're up there
Like they're really talented. I appreciate that and like I said, I really like the early stuff a lot
Some of the later stuff is okay to listen to but the early stuff is awesome like 21
Have you heard a song called have you heard a song called Tom Sawyer before? Yeah, of course. Yeah
Okay
Why does that something you can play it?
Yeah, I know how to play that on the drums. That's why I brought that up
That's one of the songs I could play on the drums. Yeah
Yeah, it's got the big role at the end a that everyone gets into
Yeah
Yeah, good stuff. I remember that I was a teen when that came out
I remember being in the arcades and that being the big song of the time
Yeah, but that music is before my time though because I'm still kind of young. I'm not that young, but I'm still young though like kind of
Yeah, yeah, not me. I mean I I became a teenager in 1980. I turned 13 in 1980. So
I was born in year 1989. Yeah
That's what I was born. Yeah
Yeah, one day you'll be in my shoes and you'll have younger people who
You know saying it happens. It's just the cycle
psyche
Yes, you ever heard of that band rush that we're talking about that's the band that I know how to play drums to
I'm good. I don't know. I was a friend that's Russian. But that's close. You get to rush. I don't know. Not really. I'm big, like, you know, rock and roll fan besides full and stuff, like.
Psyche, you don't like rock music? You don't listen to rock alternative or any kind of rock music?
I mean, I do like, I like the style. I mean, it's interesting. It's kind of interesting.
I love music, but I think it's been used a lot for programming and basically the Habistock Institute and treating the Beatles and stuff like that for every band after that and orchestrating a lot of stuff, but yeah, interesting.
So I guess somebody said this in the the comments. They said that Dom Mama said like a modern-day
Warrior mean mean stride today's Tom Sawyer mean mean pride. Hello psyche panel and chat
Okay
Anyway, what I'll say to you is think that up
Yeah, I'm not gonna make you uncomfortable. He's gonna get nice person. I don't know like
I don't know. You're basically your mental state or whatever. So I don't want to like what do you mean? He's being chill. He's cool
No, it's chill and everything. It's like, you know, people say, oh my god
Like, you know, people are saying like with like Benny like, you know, Benny's like 24 or whatever
And they're like, oh my god, like he's like, you know, Benny's retarded like he's he's not retarded
Benny's very smart and Benny's like I hear you on my show. I hear you but Mason already said he's in his 30s, right?
How old are you?
Yeah, I said I was born 1989 remember. Yeah, I know I know I don't know if it's like, you know
You're like you live with your parents and stuff like trying to like you know, do they take care of you still?
No
No, you live on your own
Yeah, I live on my own man
That's good
Okay, well if you're like starting to live on your own then no
But psyche what did I do wrong to make you think that I have I'm not as good as I was before
No, you are good as you are before but it's like I don't want to be seen as like somebody that's like
I just want to be very careful as the person posting the show not to like, you know
It's exploit anybody like I want to make sure that you're respected and so I have to respect you certainly and that's a good example
So I'll just be nicer and not not not be hitting on you anymore. Okay?
I know you're fine. I like you on the show. I actually let's say like I called for you tonight. Did I call for you tonight? You appear I
Said your name earlier. Good night. Yeah, you appear here. That's kind of weird
I think that's all he's saying, Mason. I think he's just saying he's going to lay off the hitting on you. Other than that, let's continue.
So that means we're still cool, right? We're okay with that.
We can just be bros, okay? Can we just be bros?
You know bros bros, but not no weird way, you know, like bros like, you know, just kind of like, you know
Like we're both human we're both human beings and I'll always be uh, you know
Um, you know looking out for my fail-to-man. Okay, so better than goes to me
psych
Yes
psych somebody said your mic sucks though. They said like so my name daemon said your mic sucks
I know it's Damian Damian Damian. Do you want to help me out?
Devontae and the new microphone. Okay, you want to help me out or you just want to complain about it
I have like five microphones here. It's like I what I'm supposed to like dig through all right now, and they just
Try them out. I mean I will
There's my I don't know. I just came here to have some fun tonight. Oh here. It's right
So like it's like he says this too though. He says he can't even hear you anymore. That's what they mean, sir
There it's pretty bad now you just almost dropped right out
Hold on a second. Do you hear me now a little
So what did you what did you say your name was again, man? Not psych but the you thing. Just call me thing
thing. Yeah, that's fine. So are you righty or lefty as far as a dominant hand?
Me? Yeah. I play pretty much with the left hand.
Okay, do you keep your hi hat and a crossover or you keep it more in the open like the more modern style?
Like when you cross your arms over one on an over the other one
That's how you're really supposed to play the drums that thought yeah
That's the traditional style, but a lot of drummers these days are doing like the more open set
They still have the crossover one, but they have like an open set an open hi hat right in the middle that they can
They can do it that way without doing the crossover, you know
Yeah, but most people want to see him play the drums. They have like one arm over the other arm. Yeah
I'm just saying if you watch some of the guys you watch like Danny carry from tool or
Which is named Mike from dream theater these guys they do that they they do have the crossover still
But they also have a hi-hat right in the middle of their set that they can use in between things
So they don't have to reach all the way over here
Yeah, I understand what you're saying, but I just learned to play with one arm over the other pretty much sure. Yeah
Like I said, that's true. That's the traditional way. That's the way most would learn. Yeah
Like you mean like when like your right arm goes to the hi-hat while there's like the other arm underneath it
That's just going straight right in the snare or whatever right there
Yeah
Nice psyche what was going on man
Psych you got your mic working. Yeah, I have headphones just came back in let me see if I make
Um, do you hear it right here?
Is it Ricky?
Yeah, yeah.
Can hear you good.
Page is here.
Psyche.
Absolutely.
Do you want to come up, Page?
I'm Missy Page.
I'm, um, watching a lot of old stuff today that it's like, wow.
It seems like it was like a thousand years ago.
Sounds good.
Okay, good.
I bet it sounds better.
It seems like a thousand years ago.
It was only a couple months ago.
Thing yeah, do you like dr. Pepper man?
The drink
Yeah, the drink
Yeah, I don't mind it sure
Somebody in the chat said dr. Pepper though. That's why I brought that up. Oh
Well, yeah, it's 23 flavors or 23. Yeah, I don't know
I think somebody named Eric or something like that his name is Eric Eric
Yeah, yeah
Right
Is there a control?
Does he seem like it?
I don't know. I don't know him.
If he's trolling, he's been very gentle.
Maybe not. I just don't know.
I was like, I don't.
I remember like, maybe he's like,
maybe somebody that has been nice.
No, Eric was talking about allowing Alex and ypd back up. So maybe you think he's trolling because he was talking about that
Well, that's that's up to you. I'm just saying maybe that's why you think he was trolling
I love you always play my face is what I really noticed like a lot in like some of the video
They flip talk or trip people over there. It's like I'm like being like
Probably like I'm trying to like I'm very new to what you could tell I'm very just green and I'm just trying to like
Hey, I'm having a fun panel and basically people are just making fun of me the whole time and I say I can see kind of like
I don't maybe went over my head at the time, but I really just saw it
It happens, like either you got to just take it and roll with it.
I mean, I am, I am, I'm just like, you know, the audience hates me.
I mean, I said, because people's, I have audience that will usually like, you know, like, love them or not, like...
What are you expecting adulation or something cuz you know there's gonna be some people that put you up on a pedestal
But most of us do not like that. No, no, no, no, no pedestal with that
But that's what people think is like, oh, I think it's like specials. I'm not as it was a special
asking
For like a little bit of respect because you know, I am putting it again. I don't know
Everybody hates me. I don't know. It's like I hear I've been like I'll be I'll play some of this
You know my own show also psych, you know, it's way different when you're in chat than if you're on panel
Right, like you'll say things in chat because it's just like comments
They're just they're just words that you're putting on on something digital, right? You're not actually saying a vert tube someone
It's much different
Yeah, but it was just like so, it was better.
You can see the panels were like so much fun and stuff like that,
but they're still like making fun of me the whole time.
And like nobody's respecting me.
I don't know. It's like, it was kind of like watching back.
I said, wow, I have a lot more experience now.
I can see like a lot of stuff that was going on.
I couldn't see that.
But it's still kind of like shocking.
But let me see if I have this.
Okay, but then what are your options in those cases?
Your options are to just accept that people are saying stuff and roll with it. Don't let it bother you
Let it get to you and go into a depression. I mean which one is better
I know I won't but it's like but then I'm gonna get to the conspiracy gets like so
You know it goes as far as like what they went like like I can't believe it goes and stuff like that
But it's like when you're very scary like place to live in the world or say, I don't know if I live like that
I don't know if it's like their plans or it's like the government plans or like, you know,
or like, you know, the alien vampire plans, you know, it's like, it's like some kind of
like, negative.
Sike.
Yeah.
Sike, why are you in the dark for, man?
I'm in the dark, I don't know, I don't know, I'm in the dark because nobody tells me anything.
Well, once I got it, I was going to get back on this page while I was at it.
Nobody tells you what you mean by that.
Sorry.
Anything.
But everyone has inside jokes and everyone has their own fun relationship except for me with anybody.
It's always weaponized to get to me, but I can't have normal relationship with anybody.
It's the
You might be focusing too much on on the bad comments because I've seen lots of good comments towards you people that
Sure
He'll turn on me like
If they might have said like good comments, okay, there's some good comments for a day get a mod and then like
turn on me or go
Go rogue and say
Yeah
I can't even see your face like I used to be able to see your face, but not I'll see I know I mean
I'm gonna I'm grabbing something on this channel. I air I'm just gonna show Friday the 13th party. So this is two months ago
I just want to find something that kind of old like in like just like so you can see like how it used to be on
This show is a show used to be like
Crazy oh my god, I kind of did that
How far like this was two months ago
Yeah, I want older, I want something older.
I've just been doing this for probably like six
or seven months, according to like the numbers.
This is part of the 13th video, okay.
So I'll say oldest videos.
Oldest, okay, oldest.
So let's see what I got.
When I started I started starting these huge panels and it's like but then it's like I was watching back on the panel
And it's like everyone was like
He funded me
It's like is that like a gaming headset that you have one right now
This is kind of
I have a gaming headset, so, okay, let's see.
Bring this up, okay, here we go,
I'm sorry, continue forever, okay, yeah,
share screen, and set it more to charge, okay, here we go.
Share, that's what you're gonna get, do you okay?
Psych I'm gonna mute up for a few minutes. I'm gonna go for a smoke
I'm gonna go for smoke and grab a coffee if you want to drop me down just drop me other than that
I'm just gonna leave it muted. Okay, okay?
There's an ice cream truck parked outside my house with a big satellite dish on top. What does that mean?
That's FBI, bro. That's FBI. It's not an ice cream.
Can you hear it? Oh, it's the FBI. Okay. It says FBI. It's called FBI Ice Cream.
Guys, can you hear this?
FBI Ice Cream.
Hello.
Yeah, but I don't think they're here.
No, I think you're not, bro. He was OCCB, which is Organized Crime Bureau, NYPD.
There's something called OCCB. Look it up.
It's the Organized Crime Division of NYPD.
So my uncle, start as a rookie.
Have you heard of the B?
N-A-N-A-S-P-L-I-T?
Yes, I have.
So he started on the beat in 1970s. He even has a show on A&E.
Am I still there?
Oh, that's true. About the B, A, N, A, N, A, SPLIT.
Yeah, it is. Exactly.
Mason left. The men in the split.
You ever seen the show, Runaway Squad?
I know. It's about finding all missing kids on A&E.
That's enough. I don't know.
Backward is she's I want to eat mason left thing that this is gone
And I just take off a little bit
Love you guys
Thank you for being here. Hey guys, it'll get better. Okay
What do you guys want to do? Is that beat on?
What do we do guys? Where are we going? Let me see if anyone's on.
I like different. I think I like a little bit different. I don't know.
Feels different a little bit. Let me see.
Who's on? Who's on first?
That's a baseball joke.
Um, let's see
See Danny's oh guys you want to go like raid Danny's room you go raid this room. I don't actually read him
No, I don't bother anybody. I love you guys. I'm not gonna bother anybody
Anyone wants to contact me?
Mason left damn
Okay
Spunky around or something he's gone to but I really do want to go over some stuff. Okay. I love you guys. Have a good night